[0:00]
[intro song "Wild Winds of Home" by Yin Xia
plays (0:00 - 0:27)]
Wayne: Hello and welcome to The Podcast #1:
The Future of Podcasting. My name is Wayne.
Trog: My name is Trog.
Baaulp: I'm Baaulp.
Log: I'm Log!
Gir: I'm Gir.
Wayne: And today, we're gonna be doin' a podcast.
It's the first... and the best... #1. And
I think we have some things we're gonna talk
about today. Some topics, some questions.
Log: You're really excited. I'm not talkin'
to Wayne, I'm talkin' to you, the listener,
[crosstalk] you're so excited.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Gir: You don't even realize it yet.
Baaulp: We live in your phone. I live next
to your battery and I like to walk over past
those capacitors there, close to where your
phone speaker is, and hang out at my friend
Wayne's place. We play video games on tiny
consoles. Did anyone, like, do anything interesting
these last few weeks, or play any games, or
see any movies, or anything you wanna talk
about?
Trog: [crosstalk] I did.
Log: No, next question.
Trog: What? No, I did. I did. Because I, over
the last two weeks— no, less than that,
over the last week, I watched EVERY English
episode of Dragon Ball Super, and I think
almost—
Baaulp: You just marathoned the whole thing,
like the entirety of it?
Trog: I got up to like, I don't know, Episode
30, and then took a month break, and then
came back and watched the next 40, [crosstalk]
and my review?
Baaulp: Damn.
Trog: Good. Good, although I don't know if
its, like, ACTUALLY good, or if I just really
like those characters. I'm not sure, I don't
know.
Wayne: I love Dragon Ball Z, and I really
like Dragon Ball Super, but Dragon Ball Super—
I don't know about the manga, but as an anime—I
was talking about this earlier—Dragon Ball
Super, if it was not those characters but
the same exact story, and the same exact story
mechanics, it would suck. It'd be so bad,
[crosstalk] it would be awful. It would be
so bad.
Trog: Yeah, I kinda get that same feeling.
Baaulp: So I never watched any of Super, did
they just phone it in or what?
Trog: No, no, no.
Wayne: [crosstalk] No, it's all Akira Toriyama.
Trog: It's good. It's all good. It's good,
it's just like— it's good in that weird
Dragon Ball campy-ness, I don't know, it's—
Wayne: Dragon Ball Z was already so heightened
and like, where can you take it from there
without it seeming like a fanfiction?
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: That's kinda the problem that Dragon
Ball Super has.
Trog: Exactly. It gets really silly in terms
of all the power level stuff. They have to
keep amping it up and stuff, and it gets kinda
silly, but I think it's still good, and I
still really like it, and I would definitely
recommend it, but...
Wayne: So here's the synopsis to my new fanfiction,
Dragon Ball Ultra, alright; Goku becomes so
strong, now he's a god. And he fights a god,
but he's not actually a god, it turns out.
Goku's not actually a god, he just has god-like
power levels. And then Frieza comes back from
the dead and he's GOLDEN. And then Vegeta
fights a ROBOT full of LAVA. AND THEN... and
then GOKU—
Baaulp: Does that happen? Did he fight a robot
full of lava?
Trog: Yes, he did.
Wayne: And then Evil Goku comes, and he KILLS
CHICHI!
Gir: In that order.
Trog: You missed an important part, because
everybody's favorite character, Future Trunks,
comes back AGAIN for some reason—
Wayne: [crosstalk] And he can't do shit.
Trog: And THEN Evil Goku shows up.
Wayne: And he can't do shit, because Evil
Goku is THOUSANDS of times stronger than Trunks.
Gir: I would like to touch on something real
quick, uh, Trog.
Trog: What?
Gir: Why the fuck do you hate the Pilaf Gang
so much?
Trog: I don't know—
Wayne: [crosstalk] They're annoying as shit!
Trog: Yeah, I just find them really annoying.
Gir: They're not that bad!
Trog: Like, I don't get too bothered by filler
but, yeah, I don't know. Something about any
filler involving them just made me really
upset. I think it's like... I don't know,
they're just annoying, and useless, and you
know that if they're in an episode, they're
not gonna do anything. They're just gonna,
like, yell, and be annoying.
Wayne: Yeah, it's also like, maybe it wouldn't
be that bad, but they're there too much. They
stop after a certain point but they will get,
like, 5 minutes of an episode MULTIPLE times
during an arc, [crosstalk] like in the Goku
Black arc.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Any other interesting things happen
to you this week, or topics you'd like to
talk about? Oh, I have one actually. Or Log,
you go first, since you were not involved
in that conversation at all.
Log: Yeah, welcome to the official podcast—
the Dragon Ball podcast you never knew about.
Gir: It's gonna keep happening.
Log: Here's my Dragon Ball fact: last weekend
I helped put up a fence. I've never done that
before. It's really bad, actually, you shouldn't
do it.
Wayne: You put it up from nothing? Like, you
installed the whole thing?
Log: Well, there was a preexisting fence and
it was bad. [crosstalk] So we had to—
[5:00]
Wayne: Was this a chain link fence, or was
this a picket, wooden—
Gir: Yeah, I was about to ask.
Log: It's wooden.
Gir: Wood?
Baaulp: Wood.
Log: My grandpa found a good deal on these
prebuilt sections of a wooden fence, so he
bought like, 10, and just stacked them in
the yard of my uncle's house. So today we
decided—or not today—on the weekend, we
decided to try and start putting up some of
those things, knocking down the old shitty
fence, and putting in the new wooden fence
that was good. I don't like that. It's not—
it doesn't work. You need two people to move
the pieces of fence, right, so that's already
bad. Y'know, wasps hang out there. [crosstalk]
Dirt hangs out there.
Wayne: Oh my god. Wasps are like... I have
a connection to this story in the summer that
I painted my dad's wooden fence, and wasps
were a big part of it. I'd say maybe 50% of
my time painting that fence was spent avoiding
wasps, and I fucking HATE wasps. They are
my enemy.
Gir: Yeah, I got my first wasp sting in like...
15 years.
Baaulp: What did it feel like? I've never
been stung by a wasp or a bee.
Gir: It felt like a hot needle being rammed
into me.
Trog: You know how people would describe a
pain as a stinging pain? That's where that
comes from, Baaulp.
Wayne: That's why they say it's a bee sting.
Gir: The wasp's sting felt like a sting.
Baaulp: That's the basis? I'm surprised I
haven't been stung by a wasp or anything,
because I would hang out at my friend Spencer's
house all the time [crosstalk] back in high
school, and at the—
Trog: And cover yourself in maple syrup.
Wayne: And I'd roll around underneath the
beehive, and they wouldn't even come get me.
Gir: I think they'd avoid you.
Baaulp: No, he just had a wasps nest at the
very top of his house [crosstalk] that he
could never get rid of.
Gir: That's where he kept it. He kept it there.
Trog: That he cultivated, raising wasps.
Wayne: He owned one, it was his— it was
HIS wasp nest.
Trog: "Hey guys, wanna come over and see my
cool wasp nest? I've been training them to
attack."
Wayne: "You wanna see my wasp?"
Gir: "It makes this tight noise when I hit
it."
Log: "I've raised them from birth, I know
each one."
Trog: [crosstalk] "I'm the Wasp King."
Wayne: "Wanna come to my house and get stung?"
Trog: "My name is Tyler the Wasp King, and
I will take over all of Boston."
Log: "Hey bro, you wanna do a wasp?"
Gir: He asked you to come over and get fucked
up, but he meant get attacked by wasps.
Wayne: Alright, so I've got a tangent to take
from this. So for those of you who are NOT
Baaulp and HAVE been stung by bees, what is
your worst bee sting story? Like, what's the
worst— was there ever a time where it wasn't
just ONE bee, have you ever had an encounter
like that?
Baaulp: Oh my god, that's like straight out
of RuneScape.
Gir: I didn't have multiple, but I did get
stung right on my ass.
Trog: [crosstalk] How?
Gir: That sucked.
Trog: Why were your pants off?
Gir: [crosstalk] I don't— I was a kid and
we were swimming
Wayne: Gir was mooning the bees.
Gir: Huhuhuh, check this out, little dumbasses.
Wayne: You started mooning the bees and immediately
they beelined it for your ass.
Gir: Hey, that's that kids ass!
Wayne: We know that ass, [crosstalk] go get
it!
Gir: We know that ass!
Log: It's like, y'know, the olden times where
you'd get your cat mad at you, so he'll just
take a wasp and put it underneath the cushion
of your seat right as you're about to sit
down.
Wayne: [crosstalk] What?
Gir: Was your cat Garfield?
Trog: Your cat?
Wayne: Was your cat sentient?
Baaulp: I don't think cats ever did that,
and he's trying to make a reference to Tom
and Jerry, so...
Log: Yeah, y'know, it's like back in those
days where cats wore gloves all the time.
Gir: Oh...
Trog: Oh right, where all animals wore gloves.
Log: Yeah, and then you'd fly up and you'd
take damage from both ends, [crosstalk] 'cause
you get stung, and then you fly up out of
your seat, and impact your skull on the ceiling—
Gir: And you go "AHHHH!"
Wayne: [crosstalk] How much damage?
Log: So it's like a double damage.
Wayne: How much?
Log: It's like double damage.
Gir: You get double donked.
Wayne: Alright, well, I have a bee story.
So, when I was a kid I used to have to mow
the lawn all the time, we had a really big
lawn with many levels. It was a cool place.
Gir: You make it to Level 2?
Wayne: Yeah. We also used to have a lot of
pool parties, and you know pool parties, you
got the snacks, you got the soda, you got
the soda can. And some people didn't like
to clean up after themselves, so sometimes
I'd find trash leftover from the party, and
we'd have to clean it up. And one time I was
mowin' the lawn, and I saw a can of Sprite
laying down on the lawn, [crosstalk] and I
was like, oh boy, a can of Sprite!
Baaulp: Uh oh!
Trog: I can't wait to drink this!
Gir: Can't wait to drink this soda off the
ground!
Baaulp: Oh tight, free Sprite!
Trog: So yummy!
Wayne: I cant wait to clean up this can and
please my parents for being a good— doing
a good job! And I picked it up, and underneath
that can, I saw a hole in the ground, and
I was like—
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Oh sick, free hole!
Wayne: Huh! I wonder what this hole is! And
I stuck my head in— no, I didn't do that,
[crosstalk] but I—
Trog: Ah, it's the Sprite hole.
Wayne: I observed the hole, and then I looked
at the can after I heard a buzzing coming
from the can. And you know how in the games,
and the movies, and the cartoons, when you
get stung by a bee, it's like a cloud of bees?
[10:00]
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: That's what happened.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Cloud of bees.
Baaulp: Multiple bees came out?
Wayne: From the can. I think they were like,
digger hornets or whatever, 'cause they were
diggin' a hole—
Trog: That sucks.
Gir: [crosstalk] Those things hurt.
Wayne: Cloud of bees out of the hole, out
of the can, and this is where my phobia of
bees stems from.
Log: And then you became the bee boy.
Wayne: I ran away and sat in my house forever,
and then I never went outside again.
Trog: Did you go out of your way to try to
exact revenge against ALL stinging insects?
Wayne: Yeah, I mean, later on. And then—
so, we also had a shed right next to that
hole, and that shed was really, really old,
and there was a lot of stuff in there that
we didn't really use. Basically one half of
the shed was dedicated to pool stuff that
we put away in the winter, and the other half
was dedicated to our tractor, and then there
was other stuff in there that we didn't really
touch. And we used the two shed doors that
were like these big, bulky things that were
giant, and then there was an actual house
door on it, for some reason. We never used
that house door. One day we decided to open
it, and the fucking most— the biggest wasp
nest was inside of it, and that was horrifying.
But let me tell you, the feeling of using
some Raid on that shit? Oh my god. Sweet,
sweet revenge.
Log: Does anybody USE a shed? [crosstalk]
I feel like everybody—
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Yeah, it's a place to put stuff! What
are you talkin' about?
Log: You have sheds in some houses around,
y'know. Or in the backyards or whatever. I
feel like sheds are predominately like a wildlife
cultivation center, [crosstalk] more than
a storage unit.
Wayne: They are! They absolutely are. They're
a storage unit—
Log: I've never known somebody that actually
uses their shed.
Wayne: It's complete risk/reward. The reward
is you get to put your tractor in it, and
the risk is that beavers— I mean... not
beavers...
Gir: Beavers...
Wayne: [crosstalk] Woodchucks!
Baaulp: Those beaver swarms, they make their
nests everywhere!
Wayne: Woodchucks will create a home under
it, and wasps will take it over, and then
you have to fight for your tractor.
Trog: Where else are you supposed to keep
your wasps?
Gir: I'm the outlier where, when I was a kid,
we had a shed, and it wasn't used for storage,
it was just MY personal playhouse.
Trog: [crosstalk] That seems dangerous.
Wayne: That's not a shed, then.
Log: [crosstalk] Yeah, that's a playhouse.
Gir: It was a shed!
Wayne: My neighbors had that.
Log: Well, no, it's a playhouse, it's a playhouse...
Gir: No, it's a— you don't call a fuckin'
aluminum-sided building in your backyard a
playhouse, [crosstalk] it's a fuckin' shed.
Wayne: It's a playhouse.
Baaulp: Dude, you had a cool playhouse.
Wayne: Yes it is, a child plays in there!
Trog: Anything can be a playhouse.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: Pee-wee did not live in a shed.
Wayne: Whenever I take girls home, I get them
out the car, and I say "Welcome to my playhouse,
I play in here."
Trog: And then they leave.
Gir: And then they leave, yeah!
Wayne: [crosstalk] And then they leave!
Baaulp: Tekken 7.
Gir: [crosstalk] I have a tangent for your
bug story, 'cause like being surrounded by—
Wayne: Did Baaulp just say Tekken 7?
Gir: I hope so.
Baaulp: Yeah, you said playhouse, you play
Tekken 7 there!
Trog: If you listen carefully—
Wayne: [crosstalk] You play a lot of games
in here.
Log: We drop all kinds of references in this
one.
Trog: If you listen carefully in this podcast—
Wayne: Undertale.
Trog: Baaulp will just be saying the names
of video games, and if you write them all
down and send them in, you'll win a sweepstakes.
Log: Pokémon Blue.
Gir: We'll make fun of you.
Wayne: The Banner Saga. The Banner Saga 2.
[crosstalk] The Banner Saga 3.
Gir: But yeah, your cloud of bugs story—
Log: Frostpunk.
Gir: —reminded me of when I was a child.
When I was a kid, I liked trying to get lizards.
I liked to pick up the lizards, you know what
I mean?
Trog: Hell yeah, man! [crosstalk] I liked
to pick up lizards, if you know what I'm sayin'.
Gir: You know what I'm sayin'?
Wayne: [crosstalk] YEAH, LIZARD COLLECT. LIZARD
GET.
Gir: But here's the thing—
Baaulp: I don't know why, but I like to imagine
that they wouldn't run from you [crosstalk]
and you would just pick them up nonchalantly.
Gir: They would, and I'd have to chase them.
Wayne: They didn't want to be picked up.
Gir: There was one time where I noticed a
snake, and I knew that the snakes in the area
were... safe, they were like garden snakes.
But I went to go get it, and I reached my
hand into the hole that it went into, like
"Ah man, this is a deep hole, I can't find
that snake!". I pulled my hand back out, my
hand is not my hand anymore. It is now a mass
of ants in the shape of my hand.
Wayne: You dumbass!
Trog: Why did you stick your hand in a hole!?
[crosstalk] When has that ever worked out
for anyone?
Gir: I wanted that snake, man!
Baaulp: Hold on, I just realized something.
What is with you guys and sticking your hands
in holes [crosstalk] and picking up random
cans of Sprite?
Wayne: I didn't stick— okay, in my hole
story, I didn't stick my hand in the hole.
[crosstalk] That was a joke.
Gir: I didn't know there were ants in the
hole, I thought it was just like a hole and
some rocks.
Wayne: How old were you?
Trog: Why don't you guys in the comments tell
us your favorite hole story, [crosstalk] let
us know what weird holes you've stuck your
appendages in.
Gir: I didn't know there was ants in there,
I just knew there was a snake in it!
Log: I didn't know there were ants in there.
[crosstalk] I was just gonna reach into the
snake hole!
Gir: Look, look look, don't question the—
Log: I was only intending to fish in the snake
hole!
Wayne: I didn't know there was piss in the
bottle, I thought it was a free drink!
Gir: That's... way different.
Wayne: Yes it is, [crosstalk] you thought
there was a free snake in the hole!
Gir: Yes, it is different, thank you for agreeing!
Wayne: You thought there was a free snake
in the hole, and you stuck your hand in there!
Gir: Don't question the logic of a child,
my man.
Wayne: You should have been older.
Gir: You know what, you're right.
Log: [crosstalk] Where do I begin?
Gir: Fuck you.
Baaulp: I have my own story, and then I think
we can move onto something else. I was like,
maybe 7, or like 6 years old—
[15:00]
Wayne: Should've been older.
Baaulp: Me and my neighbor were hangin' out
and we were eating Go-Gurt on the steps to
the apartment.
Trog: Then Tyler came by and was like, "Hey,
check out all these wasps I collected!"
Wayne: "Check out all these holes in my yard!",
and he put his hand down and he got sucked
in.
Log: "Hey, I got a snake down this hole over
here."
Baaulp: I thought it was a Go-Gurt hole!
Gir: When a Go-Gurt comes out of its hole,
you get seven weeks of summer.
Baaulp: No joke, we were eating Go-Gurt, and
then we started— we were just talking to
each other, but then we started feeling itchy
and then we looked down, and at some point
from under us—we were just sitting on some
steps—once a year, ant colonies will have
mating flights, where they'll actually give
birth to reproductive males and females, and
they'll have wings, and they'll fly? And so
ants just start swarming around us, and they
started flying, and I didn't know that as
a kid, I didn't know ants could have wings!
So we start freaking the fuck out, and we
ran away.
Trog: They wanted your Go-Gurt.
Wayne: EDF Origins.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: We didn't know ants had wings! We
were legitimately scared.
Trog: Hey, I didn't know ants could have wings
until you just told me right now, so...
Baaulp: Really?
Wayne: [crosstalk] I knew that.
Gir: Really?
Trog: I didn't know that.
Gir: Goodness. How do you think they get around
so easy?
Trog: I stay indoors.
Log: How's a winged ant know how to do anything?
They like, count their steps to figure out
how to get home.
Gir: Nature.
Baaulp: What?
Gir: What?
Log: Yeah, that's how they do it.
Baaulp: Whatever, I don't—
Gir: [crosstalk] They count their wing beats.
Wayne: Ants don't know math!
Gir: Ants is fuckin' dumb!
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Yeah, ants are pretty
dumb, huh?
Wayne: Counting is math, and ants cant do
that.
Baaulp: Yeah
Trog: Welcome to Bugcast.
Wayne: Ants are so dumb, if a certain ant
dies, they all just start walking in circles
until THEY die, they can't count!
Trog: Yeah, it's beautiful.
Gir: If you crush an ant, it dies, it's pathetic.
Baaulp: Ants have, what, [crosstalk] like
5 brain cells?
Wayne: WEAK. You counted them?
Gir: You looked really hard.
Baaulp: THEY did.
Trog: They counted them.
Wayne: THEY did, THEY counted them!
Trog: And they told me, they let me know.
Gir: I looked down at an ant, and it said,
"Hey, bro."
Log: Yeah, they buzzed down into my ear and
said "I have 5 of them!"
Gir: "We got 5!"
Trog: "Can I have your Go-Gurt now?"
Baaulp: Besides our various encounters with
bugs these last few days, [crosstalk] anything
else happen?
Gir: YOURS.
Wayne: Well, something funny happened at work.
I told you guys about it already, but the
viewers could hear it, [crosstalk] and then
you guys could tell your retail stories.
Baaulp: I don't think I know this story.
Wayne: Well, the other day, I was at my retail
job at an undisclosed location, I don't know
where it is.
Baaulp: Undisclosed company.
Trog: Denny's.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Dark company.
Wayne: Yes, undisclosed company.
Gir: Denny's.
Wayne: I do work at a pet store, [crosstalk]
and my job for the day--
Trog: Denny's for Pets.
Wayne: At least during that hour, at Denny's
for Pets, I was the cashier. Near the cash
register, we sell dog toys, and y'know, in
a store, customers are gonna be there. Customer
walks up, 60 year old man. He's in a red shirt.
He walks up to the table with dog toys and
starts shopping very intently, he's very focused.
And generally, if I see a customer who's not
actively looking for help, or they look like
they're very engaged in the product, I'm not
gonna say anything to them. I'm not gonna
greet them, or say "Hey, I can ring you out
over here!" 'cause they're still shopping.
So this dude, he's at the dog toy table, which
is about 10 feet away from me. Can see him
in plain sight. He picks up a stick. It's
like a stuffed lion, but it's in the shape
of a stick, it's a squeaky toy. He picks it
up, he looks at me, he looks back down at
the toy. Squeaks it ten or twelve times, looks
back up at me, smiles, squeaks it a few more
times, and he walks out the door. With the
lion in his hands. And store policy for theft
is that you're supposed to try and get their
attention and try to stop them from going
outside, but once they go outside, you cannot
leave the store anymore, because then you
are in danger. In this situation, I was so
bewildered by this man's, like, obvious lack
of stealth and lack of CARE for being stealthy
while stealing this dog toy, that I just didn't
say anything, I didn't think to. And then
by the time he walked out the door, I just
sort of followed him and looked outside, and
I saw him just walk out to his car and he
was just holding it up to his chest, and then
he got in his car and drove away.
Trog: See, I love that story, and let me tell
you why. Because now, I feel like I can steal
anything. [crosstalk] I feel like all you
need—
Gir: You just have to bewilder everyone.
Trog: You just need confidence. This just
tells me that all you need in life is enough
confidence, and you can pull off anything.
You can just shoplift, it doesn't matter.
[crosstalk] It's all yours.
Log: And also an item that you can pick up
and take without it setting off alarms.
Trog: [crosstalk] Yeah, that also helps.
Wayne: Yeah, that too. That's the one limitation.
Baaulp: I'm gonna go up to a fuckin' general
and just be like, "Oh, can I see your shiny
nuclear launch key?", and I'll jingle it to
distract him and walk away with it.
Log: Maybe you have to be able to squeak your
theft item.
Gir: Yeah, that's the secret to it.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] You have to squeak it.
Trog: Yeah, as a distraction.
Baaulp: Maybe it's not even the squeak, maybe
it was just squeezing it.
[20:00]
Baaulp: I'll just order chicken nuggets, and
I'll take one out and I'll squeeze it, and
then I'll walk away without paying.
Wayne: It was just, like, obviously he was
right in front of me, obviously he was right
there, I could see him. But it was the fact
that we made EYE CONTACT and he smiled.
Trog: 'Cause he knew!
Wayne: Like what Trog was saying, the confidence,
the raw confidence, just like, "Yeah, this
things mine." [crosstalk] I'm gonna go outside—
Trog: He knew.
Gir: "It's mine now, you little punk!"
Wayne: I'm gonna go outside and I'm gonna
hug it in the parking lot, and I'm gonna show
it to my wife, then we're gonna get in the
car and drive away [crosstalk] while the cashiers
looking.
Baaulp: Did he do that?
Wayne: Yes, he did.
Baaulp: Are you serious?
Baaulp: I have a friend who is a butcher,
[crosstalk] and he told me about this couple—
Wayne: He loves stealing lion toys.
Baaulp: What?
Gir: He loves turning old and stealing.
Wayne: Go.
Baaulp: No, he told me about this couple who
are VERY well off, and he's like, they're
very well off because they just chit-chatted,
and the guy's like a lawyer or something.
Clearly doesn't need to steal, but still tries
to steal meat from the meat department at
the grocery store he works at. And he assumes
that they do it for the thrill of it, because—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: No, that's why they're well off. They
steal their meat, they don't have to pay for
it.
Baaulp: Oh, yeah.
Trog: Meat makes up 80% of the average American
spenditures, annually, so—
Baaulp: Help me balance my budget, please.
Gir: That's how he's frugal, he doesn't buy
his meat, [crosstalk] he fucking steals it.
Wayne: 70k a year on meat.
Trog: I have a question for everybody, and
y'know, considering the idea of statue of
limitations and anything, have you ever stolen
anything from a store?
Wayne: [crosstalk] Absolutely.
Gir: Absolutely.
Trog: Wow.
Log: Not a store.
Wayne: Not a store?
Trog: 100%, I cannot think of anything I've
ever stolen, you all are psychopaths.
Wayne: I was a fucking, okay—
Gir: I haven't stolen since I was a child.
Wayne: I wasn't stealing video games, I wasn't
stealing large food items, [crosstalk] me
and my friends when we were in—
Trog: You were stealing diamonds.
Wayne: Me and my friends when we were in middle
school and high school, we were just little
fuckin' assholes, [crosstalk] we really were—
Baaulp: You guys were bad boys!
Gir: Punk ass motherfuckers.
Wayne: We would go to this shitty grocery
store where none of the workers cared about
anything—
Gir: So just all grocery store workers.
Wayne: We would just open boxes of Oreos and
eat them—
Gir: Oh, you're that little fucker I hate!
Baaulp: [crosstalk] You guys are fuckin' bad
boys!
Wayne: We used to take Hubba Bubba and chew
it up, [crosstalk] and then put it back on
the shelves.
Trog: And spit it on the ground.
Gir: Oh, you motherfucker.
Wayne: No, no no no no, we didn't do that.
Trog: [crosstalk] Put it back in the container.
Gir: I would've kicked your punk ass.
Wayne: We did take gum, but we didn't do that.
I did, on two or three occasions, we opened
an Oreo or a Chips Ahoy, and we had a few
and put it back.
Gir: I hate you.
Wayne: Which, in retrospect, yes. That was
awful.
Log: Put you in a hole.
Wayne: That was really bad, especially for
the poor woman that would buy those for their
child.
Gir: Probably some old grandma was like, "I
got you some Chips Ahoy!" and the kids like
"Grandma, there's no fucking cookies in here!"
Trog: "It's full of chewed gum!"
Baaulp: [crosstalk] "Oh no, I'm gonna cry
now!"
Wayne: There was a deli—
Gir: "You gonna cry now, you little bitch?"
Log: Well now, hold on, though. You're taking
the cookies out of the bags and eating them,
and then putting them back, but who's gonna
get tricked by your [crosstalk] shitty cookie
mess?
Wayne: It wasn't a prank, we were just hungry!
Log: Yeah, I'm saying, [crosstalk] who's gonna—
Gir: Old people! Old people!
Log: Nobody's gonna buy it, you're not gonna
get fooled!
Wayne: That's not the point!
Log: It's not like Wayne was a little 7 year
old carrying around a heat sealer, "Oh, I'll
just reseal the bag!"
Gir: You realize that those things look fine.
Wayne: Oreos and Chips Ahoy have that special
system where you open it from the top, and
then you put it back, and it reseals itself.
Trog: Yeah, you open up the top.
Gir: Yeah, that special system where there's
glue on it.
Trog: Yeah, the secret cookie glue.
Log: They didn't have that back then!
Gir: Yeah, they did.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Yeah, they didn't have
that back then.
Log: They definitely didn't.
Trog: Yeah, they did.
Wayne: They absolutely did! This was when
I was in high school and middle school, [crosstalk]
they absolutely did!
Gir: So 5 or 6 years...
Log: You were in high school!? I assumed you
were 7!
Trog: If he was 7, how would he get to the
store!?
Log: [crosstalk] He would walk, I dunno!
Gir: His mom took him.
Wayne: We just didn't give a shit! Okay, and
here's our logic, we only did this at this
one really shitty grocery store where the
managers were assholes, and all the workers
didn't give half a shit, so like, no harm
done! And also, I regret this. That's the
other thing. [crosstalk] No harm done, I regret
this!
Trog: Just thought I should throw that part
in, pretty important.
Wayne: Well, 'cause I shouldn't have been
stealing, [crosstalk] because I was just an
asshole teenager!
Trog: In case the FBI is listening.
Gir: Here's the thing, is I stole when I was
a child—
Wayne: I'm sorry, FBI!
Gir: I stole when I was a child, but I just
stole a video game cheat magazine.
Wayne: That's even— that's so much worse.
Gir: So it was like 7— yeah, okay.
Baaulp: What game was it for?
Wayne: [crosstalk] James—
Gir: It was for all games, it was a 7 dollar,
[crosstalk] here's all these game systems,
here's all the cheat codes for these games.
Trog: Oh, yeah, I've had one of those before.
Back before the internet, yeah.
Wayne: ALL games? Oh my god. You stole the
magazine with cheat codes for ALL games EVER?
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: That was so expensive.
Gir: It was pretty epic.
Wayne: That was like a 300 dollar magazine.
Baaulp: He just said it was 7 dollars!
Gir: It was 7 dollars. I went there, [crosstalk]
okay—
Wayne: Here's why you should regret your actions.
Gir: I do! Actually, I don't.
Wayne: James. James, 8 years old. Couldn't
beat Finding Nemo. Needed the infinite lives
cheat. [crosstalk] You took the last one.
[25:00]
Gir: There was another copy, I didn't take
the only one.
Wayne: Well no, you took that one, and then
someone else took the other one.
Gir: Well, that's his fucking problem, [crosstalk]
he should've got there sooner.
Wayne: He never beat Finding Nemo!
Gir: Nobody likes Finding Nemo, that game
sucked!
Wayne: I'm using Finding Nemo on the GameCube,
because I remember I had a cheat code book,
and that was one of the first things in it
for some reason.
Gir: I had Finding Nemo on the GameCube, and
that game was a pile of shit.
Trog: Yeah, that game was really bad.
Gir: It was so fucking bad.
Wayne: Games not having cheat codes where
it's just pressing a sequence of buttons at
the main menu anymore is a fucking tragedy.
Trog: [crosstalk] Yeah, they need to bring
that back.
Gir: Yeah, it's a travesty.
Baaulp: Well, that's DLC now!
Wayne: I know. It literally was! What was
that game that had DLC where it was like,
"Oh, cheat code DLC!", [crosstalk] and it—
Gir: Saints Row.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Was that Saints Row?
Trog: Was that Saints Row?
Log: Dead Rising, I think.
Wayne: That was some bullshit. Yeah, Dead
Rising as well.
Trog: What the hell, really?
Gir: Still bought it.
Wayne: Dead Rising and Saints Row both had
that.
Trog: I did not know that.
Baaulp: I am a good boy, I did not steal,
but I will say this. I just remembered this,
I might be a good boy, but I might've been
a dark boy, because I did not steal, but man—
Gir: Did I murder!
Baaulp: This one time I pulled some, like,
on the verge of almost being a little psychopath.
Because I was playing in the park, it was
just me and my parents, they took me to the
park—
Gir: ??? and killed a kid!
Baaulp: There was a family there that looked
much more well off than me, and the concept
of pen pals was just introduced to me. This
was back before most people— or, a lot of
people had internet, so if you wanted to talk
to someone you either called them or sent
them an old-fashioned letter. And I was like,
"I know what a pen pal is, I know what to
do!" Fast forward, this kids parents are buying
me McDonald's because they think I'll be this
kids pen pal, [crosstalk] and I'm pretty sure
they gave me their address and the kids name,
and I threw the paper away later.
Trog: What the fuck?
Wayne: What?
Trog: What?
Gir: Nice.
Wayne: I don't understand this story, [crosstalk]
I don't understand why your—
Gir: That's more a fault of the parents than
you.
Wayne: I don't get this at all.
Baaulp: I manipulated them into getting me
free food.
Wayne: Yes, but why did they buy you McDonald's
because you were the kids pen pal? A pen pal
is just—
Baaulp: Because they thought that kid was
gonna get a— okay. I talked to them, I remembered
them being from out of the city, and they
thought their kid was gonna get a cool Asian
pen pal friend, and become more worldly, and
I took advantage of their hospitality and
their hope, and I threw that paper in the
fucking trash when they weren't looking.
Gir: [crosstalk] That's more taking advantage
of them being dumb.
Trog: Honestly, I really like that story.
Wayne: [crosstalk] It's really good.
Trog: That reminds me of something really
fucking dumb me and my friends used to do
as small-ish children, probably like, y'know,
8 to 10 years old. We used to just ride our
bikes and wait for a car to drive by, and
then pretend to crash and see if we could
get them to stop and ask if we were alright.
Gir: [crosstalk] That's pretty good.
Trog: Looking back on it now, I can't fathom
why we thought this would be interesting,
but for some reason, it was like, if we could
pretend to crash on our bikes good enough
to get a car to stop and be like "Hey, are
you okay?", then it was great.
Wayne: Trog, you were doing insurance fraud
as a child.
Trog: Yeah. [crosstalk] Well no, because we
weren't running into the cars.
Gir: They weren't running into the cars!
Baaulp: No, they weren't crashing into the
car, they were crashing into each other!
Trog: We weren't running into each other!
Wayne: Have you seen those insurance fraud
videos, though?
Gir: Yeah.
Wayne: You don't need to touch the car, you
can just fall over near it and expect money
from them.
Trog: All we were doing, we were riding our
bikes, and then we'd just fall to the side
onto grass. And thinking back on it now, I
realize how fucked up that is, because whenever
I'm driving and I see any child on the sidewalk,
I'm in full-on panic mode, because I'm like,
"Kids are fucking dumb. If he decides to run
into the street and I can't stop my car fast
enough, my life is over."
Wayne: I have nightmares about that shit.
But what I was gonna say, did any cars ever
stop?
Trog: I think like, one, ever.
Wayne: And what happened?
Trog: What do you think happened? They stopped,
they said "Hey, are you okay?", and I was
like "Nah, I'm good." and they're like "Okay."
and they drive away!
Wayne: There's another outcome to that, though.
They could've been pissed! They could've been
fucking furious at you!
Gir: "Why are you kids hurtin' yourselves,
you little fucks?"
Wayne: Like Rocco— Like fuckin' Mega64,
Rocco Botte, he told a story at some point
about when he was a kid, he used to take toy
M16's and shoot at cars with them.
Trog: [crosstalk] Oh god. That's different,
that's way different.
Gir: That's so, so fucking reckless.
Wayne: Well yes, and he's also from a different
generation than us, where that was [crosstalk]
those kinds of toys were more—
Gir: Not acceptable, ever.
Wayne: Well yeah, [crosstalk] but more realistic
gun toys were available.
Trog: But won't land you in jail.
Wayne: Well he was a child, he was like 8.
Gir: [crosstalk] Kid jail.
Wayne: Talking about doing shitty stuff near
roads as a kid, like crashing your bikes.
When I was in like sixth grade, I did something
that could've gotten someone killed, and I
have no clue why I did it.
[30:00]
Wayne: I took a big ass rock, like a rock
maybe the size of a basketball and a half,
[crosstalk] I just put it in the middle of
the road.
Gir: What the fuck?
Trog: What the hell?
Gir: Oh, I thought you were gonna say you
threw it at a car [crosstalk] as it was passing.
Trog: Threw it at somebody!
Wayne: Oh, no! No, I put it in the middle
of the road, which is arguably more dangerous.
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Okay, 'cause when I was 8, that's what
I did, was we took pebbles, and we'd throw
'em as cars were going by.
Wayne: Oh my god.
Gir: [crosstalk] Yeah, I was a little shithead.
Trog: That's not bad. That's not unusual.
Gir: [crosstalk] It wasn't bad until I learned—
Wayne: It's not bad, but I just imagine it
actually happening, [crosstalk] where you
ding a car and fuck it up.
Gir: Yeah, no, that's what happened is one
day I finally discovered the concept of leading
your shot, and I hit a car, and they immediately
hit their fucking brakes, and I RAN.
Wayne: Hold on, how old were you?
Gir: Like 8.
Baaulp: 18.
Wayne: And you didn't understand— 18...
Trog: I was 22!
Gir: [crosstalk] 7 or 8.
Wayne: When I was 22, I found out the concept
of leading my shot! [crosstalk] That's what
I was laughing at.
Gir: Yeah, it was like 7 or 8.
Wayne: I feel like even when I was a kid,
I found out— I would know that you wouldn't
throw at it the moment you saw the car in
front of you.
Gir: Well, you had video games. We couldn't
afford video games, so I threw rocks at cars.
Wayne: That's not a thing that video games
have to teach you!
Gir: Yes it is.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Did you ever play catch?
Baaulp: Did you ever throw a ball?
Gir: No.
Wayne: Did you ever play catch with a moving
target?
Gir: No. [crosstalk] My targets all stood
still.
Trog: This just reminds me of the scene from
The Good Son where Home Alone throws a dummy—
Baaulp: Wait, sorry, I have to interrupt you.
You said everything was still, like no one
moved—
Gir: Yeah.
Baaulp: You ever played basketball?
Trog: No.
Gir: No.
Baaulp: Everyone just stands still?
Gir: When I was 8, no, I had not played basketball.
Wayne: And no one had run before. [crosstalk]
None of my friends had moved.
Gir: Nobody had ever.
Log: We're gonna put Gir and Wayne away.
Gir: I don't wanna go away.
Trog: Forever.
Wayne: Why?
Log: You've done too much.
Trog: Yeah, you guys, [crosstalk] this is
actually a sting operation.
Log: The proof has been given.
Wayne: I have another story about how I slashed
a cars tires.
Trog: Woah, what the fuck?
Gir: [crosstalk] I have another story about
how my friend almost burned his house down.
Wayne: No, I'm making jokes about crime, it
didn't actually happen.
Trog: Crime jokes.
Log: Yeah, y'know— man, I gotta talk shit
about something that I remember from years
ago. Y'know how they got fuckin' blogs out
there that are all about roleplaying as a
shoplifter?
Gir: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Wayne: Yes.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Oh yeah, yep.
Log: It makes me— it confuses me that somebody
would roleplay as a shoplifter to begin with,
'cause there's no thrill to it if you're not
actually doing it, right? [crosstalk] Like,
what's the point?
Baaulp: Well, the thrill comes from making
people online THINK you're a shoplifter, I
guess.
Log: But also the second thing that makes
me mad at it, is that they call it "lifting".
And all of their titles are like, "Lifting
Master" and "Lifting Queen" and stuff.
Wayne: Well that's 'cause they don't want
it to be like, actually— people think that
they're doing illegal shit.
Log: "Ey, I lifted two lobsters from the grocery
store today!" [crosstalk] "Lifting King!"
Wayne: It's like, "Alright, I'm gonna roleplay
as a murderer, what do I call it?" [crosstalk]
"Ah shit, I can't say that I'm murdering people
on my blog!"
Gir: "Did some murd' today."
Wayne: "I did some— I durged somebody today."
Log: "I did some slang today."
Trog: "Hey what's up, it's me masterslayer49,
and I'm gonna show you how to get 99 Runecrafting
in 4 months."
Wayne: Alright, what's step one?
Trog: Quit your job, number one. Number two,
sell all your worldly possessions except for
a computer and an internet connection, and
never sleep.
Wayne: Leave enough money to fund food for
a year.
Trog: You don't need food.
Baaulp: Only lasagna, and water, and bread.
Wayne: No, and degreased pizza!
Gir: Number three, once you get all that Runecrafting,
go ahead and give me your login information.
Wayne: I can verify that you have 99 Runecrafting,
[crosstalk] you won't know.
Trog: Only I can get 99 Runecrafting, you
have to give your account to me [crosstalk]
and I will unlock it.
Gir: You can only make it to 98.
Wayne: That last level, 98 to 99, is impossible.
Once you hit 98, I need your info.
Gir: [crosstalk] But I know a guy.
Wayne: But I also need your credit card number
to fund membership.
Gir: I know a guy who can do it.
Trog: Talking about crime and shit, I've never
stolen anything, but I've definitely tried
to scam people on RuneScape when I was like
7, is that the same?
Gir: No.
Baaulp: Yeah. Yes, that's even worse.
Trog: Not 7, I guess I was like 10.
Wayne: I scammed people all the time on Maplestory.
Maplestory used to have one of the dumbest
things ever, which was fame, and fame was
just like, once a day, you could click an
arrow on someone's profile, and it would make
a number go up for fame. And for some reason,
people would just buy it for 20k, 'cause I
think certain armor types, you needed Fame
to wear it. Which is ridiculously dumb. So
yeah, you would just say, like, "Oh, selling
Fame, 15k." and get someone to give you 15k
and then [crosstalk] not upvote.
Trog: Not do it.
Baaulp: Yeah, there's no way to verify it.
Also, I distinctly remember passing by one
person in an area where we were the only two
people there, and we were literally just walking
opposite directions, and just to be cheeky
I clicked the down arrow. They noticed, and
they immediately started following me [crosstalk]
and yelling at me.
Wayne: How did they notice? Did they have
their profile open?
[35:00]
Log: It tells you whenever you get defamed.
Wayne: Oh yeah, it does, it does. It did,
at least.
Log: That was a really poorly thought out
decision on their part. Maybe it's different
in Korea, but here in the Wild Wild West,
you were just hunting in that fucking Ludibrium
Party Quest entrance for people with exactly
20 fame and the 20 fame requirement gear on,
so you can just fucking obliterate them instantly.
Gir: I never played RuneScape, so—
Wayne: Wait, wait, wait, wait, really, was
that a—
Log: Yeah, you didn't played RuneScape?
Trog: That was Maplestory, but—
Gir: It's the same thing to me.
Wayne: Log, I need you to elaborate a little
bit. So you would bring them into the Party
Quest and defame them so that their armor
would come off?
Log: No, like the entrances, right? You got
the Lubridium Party Quest, or the Monster
Carnival, or whatever, right?
Wayne: Uh huh. Yeah, yeah.
Log: There's just huge hordes of people in
front of the entrance to the zone that everyone
went to. You just click on a guy, "Oh, what's
that? Got 20 fame?" [crosstalk] "You've got
the Shadow gear?"
Wayne: It would make their clothes eject,
literally?
Log: Yeah, you'd just hit that button and
go, "YEAH! YEAH! YES!"
Trog: I did not know that that was a system—
tying armor to something that other players
can affect, that's wild!
Log: Yeah, that's why automated reporting
systems are a bad idea, Blizzard and DotA
2 and all them. Yeah, you think that people
won't abuse that? People always go, "Oh, I
bet you were doin' something bad if you got
banned." But man, if you were a kid and you
played Maplestory, you know what its like
to just be able to destroy somebody with the
click of a button. And you won't be responsible.
That's just a fact.
Trog: Yeah, exactly. It's not a victimless
crime, it's a— you'll never get caught.
Log: Also, I wanna talk about that... I guess
more visible example of the modern age, that
Rainbow 6 Siege instant ban filter.
Trog: [crosstalk] Oh yeah, that's great.
Wayne: That's what I was gonna bring up.
Log: Just tricking people into saying the
wrong words until they lose. [crosstalk] You
just get a free win in ranked because you
tell somebody to spell "grabbing" backwards,
or something.
Trog: You just bait racism!
Wayne: Wait, spell "grabbing" backwards? What
is that?
Log: Yeah, because if you spell it backwards,
it trips off some meme swear.
Wayne: Oh, with the double B?
Log: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: And it will ban you.
Trog: I will say, though, I don't know if
that's a good or a bad thing, but I wish every
video game I played would just ban someone
instantly for saying a racial slur.
Wayne: Oh absolutely. That's a good thing,
why would you not want that in any game? I
think Siege is like, the best game ever for
adding that.
Log: It's not good if you take the game seriously,
because if Tanner the 12 year old boy gets—
[crosstalk] on your team, gets tricked into
saying a word—
Trog: Gets baited. Gets racism baited.
Log: Yeah, gets tricked into being racist,
then you're just down a player and you lose!
Wayne: I think, for me, the pleasure of seeing
that person endure that punishment is good
enough, [crosstalk] I think I would care about
that more than winning the game.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Trog: No, it's the difference between— like,
yes, if somebody is saying it on purpose,
but Log is describing a young person, not,
like—
Wayne: Oh, being tricked into doing it?
Trog: Yeah, literally being tricked into it.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Well, I think that's funny.
Trog: It is funny.
Log: "Hey, what's the name of Cartman's superhero
form?"
Wayne: Yeah, yeah.
Log: "How do you spell 'grabbing" backwards?"
"Hey man, I noticed that you're a Spanish
speaker, what's the name of that skin, Black
Ice?"
Wayne: Black Ice!?
Trog: I don't know what that one is.
Log: Well, it's because it's an English word
filter for a multinational game, [crosstalk]
and—
Trog: Oh.
Wayne: Yeah.
Log: You know how to say "black" in Spanish.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Trog: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wayne: So, the one thing I do like about this
now, is envisioning this in a physical sense,
of like, let's say that this is a net café,
and all the people— all 10 people playing
Siege are in the same room. I just imagine
a turret on the ceiling, that someone types
one of these words, they're vaporized instantly.
Gir: I like the concept, more, that they just
go *pop* and they're gone.
Trog: Disappear.
Baaulp: I walk in, I say "Hey everybody, don't
be racist!" and it just empties.
Wayne: Okay, that's the best trigger. It's
one thing to trick a child into doing it,
but the fact that it's like— people have
just said "Don't be racist." and someone says
a racist slur in response to that? [crosstalk]
That's the best way to get someone banned.
Baaulp: Immediately gets banned.
Gir: That is a really good trick.
Log: That's pretty good, that's pretty good.
But yeah, y'know, you talk about internet
cafés, those things kinda have their own
sorta setting for that. Like, you go into
a South American arcade, or internet café,
or something, you see a KOF machine, you're
gonna see a sign that says "If you pick Omega
Rugal, somebody's gonna fight you in real
life."
[40:00]
Wayne: Hang on, is this real?
Log: I mean, that's just how it is in some
of these arcades and stuff. It's like, "Oh
yeah, I'll fuck you up if you grab me! If
you pick Omega Rugal, you're as good as dead."
Wayne: Oh, I remember hearing stories about
that! And like Street Fighter 2 and shit.
Baaulp: Yeah, arcades were freaking NUTS!
Trog: Because you're paying real money!
Baaulp: They had house rules for a lot of
arcades!
Log: [crosstalk] There's a news story—
Wayne: "Use grabs, you fuckin' pussy!"
Log: There's a news story a while back, after—
because there's an arcade in China, where
two guys were playing KOF '97, and somebody
did a wakeup super and won, and went over
and stabbed the guy who lost.
Wayne: Oh my— wait, he— he WON and then
stabbed that guy who LOST!?
Log: Yup!
Trog: Now, look. That's a mistranslation,
they were playing a Shadow Game, and when
he lost, he lost his soul.
Gir: He got sent to the Shadow Realm.
Wayne: [crosstalk] He had to drain his blood.
Baaulp: Dude, arcades— maybe arcades are
nice in Japan, but arcades in other countries
were like— you had to be ready to throw
down in game and IRL. It's one of the reasons
why I'm not into fighting games. When I was
a kid, we lived right next to an arcade. One
night, I was in bed, I was asleep. I woke
up because I heard a bang. I was like, "Oh,
it's China, it must be someone just, I dunno,
setting off fireworks for some random reason."
I wake up the next day, and my cousin who
we lived with—'cause we lived with my uncle—was
getting a stern lecture. He didn't do anything
wrong, but he was like, "Hey, you can never
go to that arcade, and you can never bring
me to that arcade ever again, because someone
got shot there last night."
Wayne: [crosstalk] Oh my god!
Trog: Jesus. What do you think he did?
Baaulp: I think he still snuck over to the
arcade and played, 'cause I think Street Fighter
2 just came out or whatever, so there's multiple
Street Fighter 2 arcade machines or something,
but he never brought me, and I never got good
at fighting games because of it.
Wayne: I think I'm going to be thinking about
that wakeup super into stab story forever.
Baaulp: I love that he was like, "Yeah, I
won! Clearly I deserve to SURVIVE IRL!"
Wayne: The fucking injury to insult of that.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Just, "Yeah, I win! Now I'm going to
kill you."
Gir: [crosstalk] "I win!" *stabbing noises*
Trog: Well, not kill, you can be stabbed in
a lot of different places, and they don't
all end fatally.
Log: Yeah, good ending to the story, I'm pretty
sure the guy that got stabbed survived, and
the both of them are friends.
Trog: Alright, well, [crosstalk] sometimes
you just gotta—
Gir: What? That's an even stranger twist.
Trog: Hey, hey, hey. I'll be honest, whenever
I was big into Tekken 7, if I was in the same
room as you guys while I was playing that
game, I probably would've stabbed you too.
Fuck Tekken.
Wayne: You were talking about stabbing them
in nonfatal places, and now I'm imagining
he wins, and he's so excited, he doesn't go
and stab him in the chest like a violent attack,
he just goes like, "Yeah, alright!", and then
he just stabs him in his pinky toe. Just something
very nonpermanent.
Gir: He pulls his knife out and he's like,
"Where is this NOT going to kill you?"
Wayne: [crosstalk] I just wanna hurt you a
little bit.
Trog: Well, you didn't read the whole story,
he actually— his left hand was just a sword,
and he tried to give him a high five. He tried
to shake his hand, say good game.
Gir: [crosstalk] GG, dude.
Wayne: Yeah, and he stabbed. [crosstalk] He
did a stabbing motion for his high five, for
some reason.
Trog: Yeah.
[intermission music “Sento Gakuen” from
Cutey Honey OST plays (43:24-43:38)]
Baaulp: Yeah, we learned a lot. We learned
a lot about Dragon Ball Super, about bugs,
about CRIME! We're all criminals, apparently.
[crosstalk] All child crimes.
Wayne: We learned about my criminal history.
Log: I'm a good boy.
Wayne: Well, mine was teen crimes, to be fair.
[crosstalk] The teen crime of eating three
cookies.
Baaulp: Let's answer some of your questions.
Gir: Bastard.
Trog: If you want to have your question read
and answered on this podcast, join the WayneRadioTV
Discord, which I assume we'll have a link
somewhere.
Wayne: Yeah, scroll down. Look down, [crosstalk]
I'm pointing down over there.
Baaulp: Look around you, it could be in real
life!
Trog: [crosstalk] Yeah, you never know.
Log: Yeah, you havin' trouble gettin' your
questions read on My Brother, My Brother,
and Me? Well, you're in luck, [crosstalk]
here's some other place that takes questions,
and—
Wayne: We'll read anything!
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: We'll answer ANYTHING.
Log: Yeah, we'll read anything!
Gir: We're fuckin' dumb!
Log: Also, you're competing with like, ten
other people!
???: Easy.
Trog: Yeah, exactly. You are essentially guaranteed
an answer, can't guarantee whether or not
that answer will be sufficient for you. But—
Wayne: Unless your question is bad.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: You want some F-Grade McElroy's?
Trog: Yeah, [crosstalk] we're not just like
the B-Team, we're like the J-Team.
Wayne: Well, this isn't really an advice—
Log: Yeah, we're not—
Trog: This is not advice.
Wayne: This is not an advice show like the
McElroy's.
Baaulp: Yeah, why do you think we're F-Grade?
Wayne: [crosstalk] We can't help you.
Baaulp: We failed the inspection.
Wayne: If you want help, we can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Log: Yeah, you want help from criminals? No.
Gir: I'll tell you what I did when I was a
kid, but don't expect any advice.
[45:00]
Trog: So this first question is from MysteryDruids,
and I really like this question 'cause it
really resonates with me personally, I'm curious
to hear what you guys have to say. But he
asks, "What's the game from your childhood
you went back and played as an adult, and
realized you had terrible taste in games as
a child?"
Gir: 40 Winks.
Trog: [crosstalk] What is that?
Wayne: The flash game from nick.com?
Gir: No, PlayStation game. Look it up.
Wayne: I dunno what that is, [crosstalk] tell
me about it.
Trog: I've never heard of that.
Baaulp: Yeah, what?
Gir: I loved it as a kid, I played it again
when I was, like, [crosstalk] I played it
like 3 or 4—
Wayne: Well, what is it?
Trog: Yeah, what kind of game?
Gir: It's like— I like, expunged it from
my memory. [crosstalk] I couldn't even tell
you anymore.
Trog: It's gone.
Baaulp: Good job. Good job, I guess, for getting
it out of your head. I know what my game is
for this question. Simpson's Treehouse of
Horror for the Nintendo— Game Boy Color.
I was poor, my parents had just bought me
my Game Boy Color, which was like, my first
game console. It was my birthday, and I was
like, "Hey, I have one game, like one video
game. Just one. Can I have more?" and they're
like "Sure, it's your birthday.", they bought
me two games. They bought me a port of Mario
Bros., like, the original, on Gameboy Color—
Trog: Oh, I had that, that was good.
Baaulp: They also bought me Simpsons Treehouse
of Horror, and I'm pretty sure I picked that
one 'cause I liked the Simpsons. That game
was trash. I played the hell out of it as
a kid, it is not good. It's like, it's just
a really shitty platformer with, like, really—
way too tight controls. The jump was like—
you couldn't control it, you just jumped a
set distance, and that's it.
Wayne: For my game, it was not one that I've
played in recent time. Like, I did not go
back and play it and then say "Oh man, this
is ass". I just remember loving this when
I was a kid, and then thinking back on it,
and seeing it. I dunno what the fuck I was
thinking, and this is the game Rugrats in
Paris.
Trog: Oh my god.
Wayne: Which came on a black N64 cartridge,
[crosstalk] and I do not know why.
Trog: Yup.
Wayne: But— so there were other Rugrats
games. There were tons of them. There was
one on PS1, it was a platformer. You play
as Tommy Pickles, you gotta find your Reptar
puzzle, it was great! It was fun. I'm pretty
sure in that game, there's a level where you
have to jump over electrified water, and if
you hit it, you are a baby and you die of
electrocution. That's unrelated. Rugrats in
Paris was basically just a game where you
walked around and then you went to an attraction
in a park and you played minigames to get
tickets. I don't remember too much about those
minigames, but the unbearably bad part of
this game, navigating? I apparently didn't
remember this at all. It was like, tank controls,
and you walked at the speed of a 2 year old
on— like, bipedally. [crosstalk] Not crawling.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: It was so fucking bad. [crosstalk]
I don't know how I enjoyed that as a child.
Gir: It's realistic.
Log: You walk at the speed of a Rugrat.
Gir: [crosstalk] Yeah, it's realistic.
Wayne: I mean, yes, but— yes, but, I dunno.
I played it a lot. I don't know why I did.
I loved it.
Gir: [crosstalk] You were dumb.
Trog: You know, that's funny, that's a really
good segue into mine, because I have two in
mind that I both— I literally still own
them, they're sitting in my living room in
a box right now. The first one is Glover.
I had Glover for the N64 as a kid, and I think
the reason I didn't realize how bad it was
as a kid, is that, I was really bad at video
games and like, wasn't good enough to finish
a lot of them at that age. So I didn't realize,
like, it never even crossed my mind that Glover
was hard was because it controlled like fucking
shit, and I just thought I was bad at video
games. But then I went back and played it
as an adult, and I'm like "Oh no, this game
is still hard, because it controls like fucking
shit, and it's terrible!" So there's that
one, and the second one is Rugrats Scavenger
Hunt, and I don't know how, [crosstalk] I—
Wayne: What? For what console?
Gir: Two Rugrats.
Trog: I don't know how I got that game. I
think I asked for it, which was the weird
part, [crosstalk] but I don't have—
Wayne: What console? What console?
Trog: N64.
Wayne: What? What is this game?
Trog: It's called Rugrat Scavenger Hunt, it's
a board game, but not like Mario Party where
there's like, games to do. It's just a board
game. It's just a digital board game where
you roll dice and you walk around as the Rugrats.
And I don't know why I wanted this as a kid,
it doesn't make any sense. And it like, perplexes
me any time I remember that I own that game.
Wayne: Y'know, this is unrelated, but when
I was a kid— when I was young, when I was
like, really really young, I played N64. And
like, I don't think I understood how to get
games. Most— I had a couple games that I
just HAD, I never got more, and then I just
rented all the others. I didn't understand
the concept of buying a game for a really
long time. I don't know why. And then I got
like, Banjo-Tooie for Christmas, and I played
that game forever. I probably have like, 300
hours on Banjo-Tooie just as a child. But
uh, anybody else have any other bad childhood
games?
[50:00]
Log: Y'know, it's funny, 'cause like, I'm
realizing how rare it is for me to actually
go back to childhood games ever.
Wayne: Yeah, me too.
Log: I don't know if I've had this situation
just 'cause of like, how few games I played
in my childhood that I actually went back
to ever.
Trog: Really?
Wayne: Yeah.
Log: I dunno, games that I have gone— I
don't even know if this can count as "gone
back to", but like, Soulcalibur 2, I played
a lot of that. That feels even better, I played
that this weekend. Paper Mario, [crosstalk]
still Grade A.
Trog: Yeah, that games still great.
Log: A plus.
Gir: So the answer is no, [crosstalk] there's
no old games you dislike.
Log: SSX 3, [crosstalk] I played that on Dolphin
like a year ago or something, still pretty
good.
Baaulp: Oh hell yeah.
Log: There's a lot of games that I remember
playing the shit out of, like Mario and Luigi
Superstar Saga, and like, one of the Lord
of the Rings games, and like, Rayman, like
the original and stuff. But like, I haven't
played those games since I was a kid.
Baaulp: Dude, you just had good taste as a
kid.
Trog: Yeah, I was about to say, is what you're
saying just that you had really good taste
as a kid, and you didn't have any bad games?
Log: Well, it's just like, if there was a
bad game, [crosstalk] I recognized it?
Trog: You don't remember it?
Log: Like I bought, what's it called, Amazing
Island?
Trog: I have no idea, [crosstalk] what is
that?
Log: Do you remember that game?
Trog: [crosstalk] No.
Gir: No one knows what that is.
Log: Let me make sure that that's the name
of it.
Gir: Oops, it was Lego Island.
Log: Yeah, Amazing Island for the GameCube.
I'll link—
Wayne: I know Amazing Island.
Log: I'll link the picture of the box art.
[crosstalk] Here, check it out.
Trog: I have no idea what this is.
Log: Yeah, so I spent 50 dollars on this game
when it came out.
Gir: Yeesh.
Log: Whenever I was like, probably 10. And
just— it took me about a week or so, but
at that point I was like, "Yeah, I recognize
this as trash. This is unplayable."
Wayne: Okay, uh, one more video game related
question from me, myself. This is just one
I'm curious about. Did any of you guys play
any video games before you could read?
Baaulp: No.
Trog: Hm, [crosstalk] that's a good question.
Gir: Maybe.
Wayne: 'Cause I definitely did.
Trog: [crosstalk] Um... man, I dunno!
Log: Um... whenever I was like, 4, I got ahold
of some other kids Game Boy with a Pokémon
game in it, and I managed to overwrite the
save somehow.
Gir: Oh nice. That was like, my biggest fear,
was my little sister doing that.
Wayne: I played— I mean, how old were you
guys when you learned to read? That's another
question.
Gir: I don't fuckin' know.
Log: Honestly, it was either 4 or 5. [crosstalk]
I dunno.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: For me it was 5 or 6.
Trog: [crosstalk] Somewhere around 4 or 5,
but I think—
Baaulp: I learned how to read at 5, 'cause
that's also when I came to America.
Wayne: For me it was like 5 or 6. When I was
4— well, I turned 5 the same year the Game
Boy Advance released, but um— Yeah, I turned
5 in 2001. And that was the same year the
Game Boy Advance released, but that was also
a little bit after the Game Boy Advance released.
So at this time I was 4 years old, my brother
and my sister had Golden Sun, an RPG. And
I pretty much— when I was a kid, if there
was a video game, I wanted to play it. I didn't
care what it was, I saw cool colors on that
box, it was like "Hell yeah, gimme that shit."
Gir: Oh, that's a wordy game.
Wayne: Yeah, it's a very wordy game! But I
didn't even get to play the game, because
I launched it and got to the main menu, couldn't
read the words on the main menu, 'cause I
didn't know how to read. Navigated the menu
within one try. It wasn't trial and error,
just the first thing I did, was erase ALL
the saves.
Trog: Oh no.
Wayne: And my brother and sister were so mad
at me. And I did this AGAIN with, um... what
was the other game? Ocarina of Time. I wiped
the saves on that accidentally.
Trog: Oh man.
Wayne: I'm pretty sure I did this with Banjo-Tooie
as well. [crosstalk] I wiped the saves on
that.
Baaulp: You're a monster.
Gir: I would've kicked your ass.
Wayne: It was accidental EVERY time. But I
just managed— every single time navigating
the menus, I managed to wipe the saves trying
to access the game.
Baaulp: Gir, real quick, [crosstalk] do you
have an answer for that question?
Gir: I already said.
Trog: He said 1000 Winks or whatever.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Oh yeah, that's right,
what the fuck is that?
Gir: 40 Winks.
Trog: 40 Winks, not 1000.
Wayne: 1000 Winks!
Trog: I'll be honest, Wayne, what you asked
has me so fucked up right now, 'cause I can't
remember ever not knowing how to read, and
I know that's not true, I know I wasn't born
and immediately knew how to read, [crosstalk]
but I can't—
Gir: 'Cause it was like, over 20 years ago.
Trog: I know, [crosstalk] but like, it's crazy!
Wayne: I can remember this— I think these
memories of deleting these save files are
what ties the memory [crosstalk] of not knowing
how to read and what that was like to my memory.
Trog: Yeah, that's probably— I probably
just don't have any strong memories of that.
Log: [crosstalk] Hey, hey—
Baaulp: Can we get uh, can we move onto the
next question?
Log: Well, hold on.
Wayne: Hold on.
Trog: Wait.
Baaulp: Okay.
Wayne: We’re having a good conversation.
Log: How old are you whenever you go to preschool?
If you go to preschool.
Gir: Like 5.
Trog: Probably 4.
Wayne: 5.
Trog: No, [crosstalk] I think you're 4.
Gir: Between 4 and 5.
Trog: You're between 4 and 5.
Wayne: No, yeah, it's 4. 'Cause you go to
kindergarten at 6, right?
Trog: No, [crosstalk] you go to kindergarten
at— well, you can, it depends on when you're
born.
Log: No, 5. You go to kindergarten at 5.
Trog: It's either 5 or 6.
Log: Like, I dunno, [crosstalk] I know I knew—
Wayne: I went when I was 10.
Log: I know I knew how to read in preschool,
because I distinctly remember they had mats
with peoples names on them, and I remember
just looking at one that said "Ray" on it.
Trog: Well there you go.
[55:00]
Wayne: I think around that time, I was learning
to read at a basic level, but like, I didn't—
it wasn't good enough that I could read like,
"New Game" "Erase All Save Files", like, those
aren't words that I was trained to read as
a 4 year old.
Log: But also—
Baaulp: That's what you think.
Log: I have like, some—
Wayne: That IS what I think, because I couldn't
read them, what the f— what?
Log: I think the earliest memory I have, and
I don't know why— I feel like I got hit
by a Men in Black memory fazer whenever I
was 2 years old, because I remember there
was a point— I was 2 years old, I was just
standing there, and suddenly I realized, "Hey,
I can talk!", and I just explained that to
my mom. "I can talk!", and she's like, "Yeah!",
and I just moved on with my life.
Trog: That's really good.
Log: And that's the earliest point that I
remember, so maybe just up until then, [crosstalk]
I just like, forgot myself.
Wayne: I like the idea that those were actually
your first words.
Trog: Well, Log, you realize whenever you
are a very young child, your brain literally
isn't developed enough to form memories, that's
probably why you don't remember.
Log: Well, I just think it's— I think it's
funny to imagine it like that, though.
Gir: I had an epiphany like that when I was
young, too. I must've been 3 or 4, and in
the middle of the night I suddenly woke up
and was like, "I can remember some stuff I
did.", I had the realization that I can remember
the past.
Trog: Man, my memory sucks compared to you
guys.
Baaulp: I distinctly remember my first memory.
I was asleep, I woke up like a drunk person
would, where I was like, "Wh-wh-what's going
on, what's happening?", and my moms like,
"Are you okay? You were asleep.", and I was
like, "Oh yeah, okay, cool.", and I went back
to sleep.
Trog: That's the most Baaulp thing I've ever
heard.
Wayne: I have like, 10 memories of falling
off my parents bed, the same exact way.
Baaulp: Holy shit!
Trog: Okay, I'm gonna read the—
Wayne: I used to roll off the bed so many
times, we should do a new question now, [crosstalk]
because we've been talking about this forever.
Trog: Yeah, we— we gotta, we gotta, we gotta—
Gir: Stay on topic here.
Trog: Okay, we have a question from friend
of the show Mira, who asks, "What is your
favorite bread item, and what is your least
favorite?"
Gir: I like garlic bread, but I don't like
wet bread.
Wayne: My lea—
Trog: Hold on, wait wait wait, before anybody
else goes, I just wanna ask, is everybody's
going to be garlic bread? [crosstalk] Because
mine—
Wayne: No. It's not my favorite.
Baaulp: No.
Trog: Okay, I'm just curious 'cause mine is
definitely garlic bread.
Baaulp: Yeah, garlic bread's good.
Gir: If not garlic bread, then banana bread.
Wayne: Alright, I have both of mine prepped.
One of the answers probably won't make sense
to anyone, 'cause I don't really know how
else to describe it, but uh... least favorite.
12 grain bread. I think it's 12 grain, I think
that's what they call it. [crosstalk] Maybe
it's like 15 grain, or something like that.
Gir: Is that the one with seeds all through
it?
Wayne: It's the ones with seeds in it, but—
it's the one with seeds in it that feel like
you're biting into flesh.
Trog: What the hell?
Wayne: It's a very fleshy nut, or seed, or
something in it. [crosstalk] It's just gross.
Trog: I've never had that before.
Log: Well, does it taste like anything, [crosstalk]
or is it just the texture?
Gir: It tastes like wheat bread.
Wayne: It's the texture. Well, it tastes like
a very strong whole grain bread, but I'll
eat whole grain. I'll eat that, whole wheat,
or whatever it is. It tastes like a very strong
whole wheat bread with the seeds in it. But
its that texture of just biting into this
chunky, meaty seed, [crosstalk] I hate it.
Gir: It's kind of leathery.
Wayne: Yeah, it's gross. [crosstalk] And my
favorite—
Gir: Not super great.
Wayne: Actually, I'll— someone else go,
I'll get back to my favorite, I gotta think
about this.
Baaulp: 'Cause you can't name cornbread or
uh, [crosstalk] garlic bread?
Wayne: No, it's not cornbread.
Log: Y'know, the shitty one out there, that
rye stuff.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I love rye!
Trog: [crosstalk] I don't like rye either.
Wayne: Have you ever had rye pumpernickel
swirl?
Log: That's not a— that's not a bread taste,
I'm pretty sure. Pumpernickel's the other
one that doesn't taste like bread, right?
Trog: I mean, they're bread, [crosstalk] so
you're technically wrong, but...
Wayne: It tastes like bread.
Log: [crosstalk] What does pumpernickel look
like? I gotta, I gotta—
Wayne: Bread is not a flavor. Bread is a texture.
Trog: Bread is not a flavor, you're right.
Wayne: It's true!
Baaulp: You guys suck at this. I'm gonna go
next. [crosstalk] I like... cornbread—
Log: Oh wait, pumpernickel's fine.
Wayne: Log was not done, but okay.
Trog: Log wasn't done.
Log: Yeah, wait— [crosstalk] OR is pumpernickel
the bad one?
Trog: Cut this out.
Wayne: Baaulp, YOU suck, because you suck
at podcasting!
Baaulp: What?
Log: Okay, yeah, yeah— okay, yeah—
Gir: Every fucking time!
Log: I think if you gave me a pumpernickel
rye swirl bread, I would die on impact.
Wayne: No, it's so good!
Log: Those are the two worst flavors of bread
in existence by far.
Wayne: It's got like a sour-ish kind of taste,
with a very savory flavor. It's so good, it's
so good with like, a turkey cheese mayo, just
somethin' simple on that... Mmm!
Log: It tastes like you've got a weird perfume,
like a weird— like you've somehow got a
smell on your bread, [crosstalk] and you're
tasting the smell.
Gir: Potpourri bread.
Wayne: You gotta have the Jewish bake!
Log: What— okay!
Gir: What!
Log: [crosstalk] Don't know what that means!
Wayne: That's what its called! I'm pretty
sure that's what its called. Y'know, is Pepperidge
Farms the company with the bread and the goldfish?
Gir: Oh yeah, I remember them.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Pepperidge Farms makes— I think its
called like, Jewish Bake Rye Pumpernickel
Swirl, or maybe it's like, Hebrew, I dunno—
Log: I just found an image on Google Images
of Pepperidge Farms Jewish Pumpernickel Dark
Pump.
Gir: Dark Pump!
Wayne: No, that's not what I'm talking about!
It's Rye Pumpernickel Swirl!
Trog: No, [crosstalk] it's Dark Pump!
Wayne: It is definitely Jewish, though.
Log: I think that those two are very disappointing.
[1:00:00]
Log: However, I will give you an insight into
a good bread item. Recently, I've been getting
into new bread.
Gir: Experimental breads.
Log: Yeah. Have you guys ever had bread pudding?
Gir: [crosstalk] Yeah, I hate it.
Trog: Uh, I have.
Wayne: I don't think so! [crosstalk] I don't
think I've ever had it.
Gir: I change my mind, that's my least favorite
bread item, [crosstalk] is fucking bread pudding.
Wayne: Really? Never had it.
Log: So... I think there's like, a lot of
different kinds, 'cause I mean, it just depends
on what bread you have. But recently, I've
had bread pudding, and like... I've never
had bread pudding before this past month.
But I've had it a couple times this past month,
since... pretty much since I've started my
job, and it's like, "Mmm. That's some good
stuff."
Gir: Nope, can't stand that shit.
Log: There was a day where I had access to
a dessert bar with unlimited desserts that
had bread pudding at it. That was some nice
times. I almost got it today, but I resisted
because it costed 3 dollars.
Gir: How 'bout you, Baaulp?
Trog: It's the best bread you've ever had,
but I refuse to spend any more than 2 dollars
on it.
Log: Well, it's just that the meal that I
already had costed like, 10.
Trog: Yeah, no, I get you. [crosstalk] I was
just making fun of you.
Gir: I wouldn't spend more than 3 dollars.
Baaulp: My favorite bread, cornbread. I can
inhale that stuff.
Wayne: Cornbread is pretty good.
Baaulp: Cornbread is sooo fucking good.
Wayne: I like a cornbread.
Log: Do you like it with the corn in it, or
the corn, like, [crosstalk] hidden?
Gir: Out of it.
Baaulp: Uh, I hope the corn is not just still
in chunks.
Wayne: Is chunky cornbread a thing?
Log: Yeah, [crosstalk] there's chunky cornbread.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Wayne: Ew! EW! [crosstalk] Who would eat that
shit? That's vile!
Log: You can have cornbread with like, visible
corn in it.
Baaulp: That’s gross.
Wayne: That's fucking vile!
Trog: I guess you're not as big of a cornbread
fan as you thought.
Gir: Cornbread's supposed to be made of corn
MEAL, not actual corn.
Baaulp: Yeah, not— [crosstalk] it's corn
MEAL, not corn. Corn.
Log: Y'all city slickers never been down to
the south, we got—
Gir: I HAVE, and they don't eat it there.
Log: We got a different whole view of corn
'round here. [crosstalk] We put it right in
the bread.
Trog: We put wasps in our cornbread.
Gir: We put wasps— we pull it out of our
corn holes!
Wayne: Log, is your cornbread chunky?
Log: I don't eat cornbread very much.
Wayne: Okay.
Log: Usually it's not, but sometimes it is.
Baaulp: Well, try smooth cornbread. Maybe
you'll like it more.
Wayne: It's so good, if your cornbread is
smooth. Mmm! It's like a cornish butter.
Baaulp: The next time you guys come to Boston,
we're gonna have to try to go to a place called
Fat Cat. No matter what you get, they bring
out cornbread. [crosstalk] And like—
Gir: This is an advertisement.
Baaulp: Honey butter, and hummus, it's so
good.
Trog: Yeah, no free plugs, Baaulp. Come on.
Log: [crosstalk] Cornbread and hummus?
Wayne: No locations, no locations.
Trog: They gotta pay us if they want advertising.
Gir: Woah, wait, yeah. That's a weird ass
combo. Cornbread and hummus?
Baaulp: It's so good. It's all so good, I've
put it all in my mouth.
Trog: Yeah, that doesn't sound that bad.
Wayne: I could eat that. That— oh, that
just sparked a fucking culinary brain blast.
That sounds delicious.
Baaulp: Anyway—
Wayne: Okay, I wanna hear your least favorite,
'cause I think it could be the biggest upset.
Log: Oh no, hold on!
Wayne: What?
Log: This is a Mira question, and I got like
a fuckin'... amnesia revival, 'cause you said
brain blast. 'Cause I just remembered something
Mira talked about where he had his dream where
he was watching two people argue, and it got
like— it did like a brain blast camera pan
into the guys brain, and instead of him saying
"brain blast" at the end, he just burped really
aggressively.
Wayne: Okay, Baaulp, least favorite bread
item.
Baaulp: My least favorite bread? I gotta go
with Log. I don't like rye, I don't like pumpernickel.
Trog: Ooh, yeah. [crosstalk] Fuck 'em!
Wayne: Pumper— ugh. Fuck you! I must be
the only one that likes it, [crosstalk] I
love it.
Trog: You are!
Baaulp: You got a weird tongue.
Gir: I have no strong opinion.
Wayne: It's an aged flavor. It requires a
very— particular taste.
Baaulp: I don't want my bread old or sour.
Log: I don’t— I don’t like ‘em.
Wayne: It's not old! [crosstalk] And it's
not sour!
Trog: It's not sour. That's sourdough.
Wayne: You don't like sourdough?
Baaulp: No.
Trog: I like sourdough.
Gir: I like sourdough.
Trog: Sourdough's good.
Wayne: It has a— it's like a minor sour
flavor, but it's not literally sour.
Gir: Hey, you ever dip au jus— uh— dub—
dip sou— fuckin' Jesus. Hold on, I'm havin'
a brain meltdown.
Baaulp: *buuuurp*
Gir: You ever dip sourdough bread into au
jus sauce?
Wayne: Au jus sauce?
Log: Probably.
Trog: No, but that sounds really good.
Baaulp: I've dipped other breads into au jus
sauce.
Gir: It's super fucking good.
Wayne: I don't know what that is.
Trog: You've never had a french dip?
Gir: It's watery gravy.
Wayne: Oh, I've had french dip.
Gir: I'll give you a french dip.
Trog: [crosstalk] That's the kind of sauce
in a french dip.
Wayne: I didn't know that's what that was
called.
Trog: Wayne, did you say your favorite bread—
[crosstalk] is it cornbread?
Wayne: I haven't said my favorite yet, but
I'm gonna go over some runners-up, because
I'm having a real hard time picking it. It's
not cornbread. You know what's really good?
Bread bowls. Bread bowls for soup. [crosstalk]
That shit's delicious.
Baaulp: But that's not like, a type of bread.
Trog: Yeah. No, that counts. That counts as
a bread item.
Wayne: But that is a flavor, [crosstalk] because
it's a type of sourdough.
Gir: That's a shape of bread.
Trog: The question was not the—
Wayne: It's a type of sourdough. It's a specific
type of bread that makes bread bowls.
Baaulp: Oh my god.
Trog: [crosstalk] The question was not—
Gir: What shape of bread do you like?
Trog: Look. The question was "favorite bread
item". It didn't say, like, type of bread.
[crosstalk] So it could be a pretzel.
Gir: That's fair.
Wayne: Yeah, I like bread armor. Bread castle.
Trog: Yeah.
Baaulp: Eh.
Gir: Move on.
Wayne: Did that concept just like, flatline
you guys?
Trog: [crosstalk] Eh. No, I'm good.
Gir: Yes.
[1:05:00]
Wayne: I picked a bread item, what-the-fuck
do you want?
Gir: [crosstalk] What-the-fuck?
Trog: No, it's good.
Wayne: Okay, so other bread item runners-up.
Naan. Naan is so good. [crosstalk] I love
naan.
Trog: Oh yeah, naan's good too.
Wayne: Naan is delicious.
Gir: It's a naan-bread.
Wayne: But I think number 1— It's just this—
like, Italian bread, but its specifically
from this one restaurant, they give you these
rolls, Bertucci's, it's a chain, I was talking
about these the other week, they're so good.
They're hot, they're fresh. [crosstalk] They're
good. This is my ???.
Baaulp: Hold up, hold up. The rolls they give
you for free at Bertucci's is your number
1?
Wayne: Yes! Those are so good.
Baaulp: Come on, man.
Trog: [crosstalk] Mine is just garlic bread,
and garlic bread is—
Wayne: Have you been to Bertucci's?
Baaulp: Yes!
Wayne: Those shits are so good.
Baaulp: That's not even the garlic bread,
oh my fucking god.
Wayne: It's not garlic bread! It's fluffy,
fresh baked, Italiano bread, my friend.
Log: Have you ever been to the House of Flying
Rolls?
Wayne: No! Next question.
Gir: Is that a church?
Trog: Wait, hang on, this just reminded me,
and then we'll move on. But since you got
to do two, I wanna say that my runner-up is
those Pillsbury pull-apart biscuits where
you bake them, and they turn into like, magical
layers, [crosstalk] and you peel 'em apart.
Wayne: Oh, like dinner rolls?
Trog: [crosstalk] I don't know exactly what
they are.
Gir: Put honey on those, and they're even
better.
Trog: Yeah, those are hella good. Alright,
next question.
Log: I caught a roll at the House of Flying
Rolls and I cried 'cause it was hot.
Trog: Next question we have from KingMusicManz
who says, "Tips on DMing and playing D&D?"
Gir: Oh, this is not for me!
Log: Alright, here's the Log Advice. You've
never seen me in action, so like, you might
be thinking "Who the fuck is this guy? He
just plays as Porky Bashwagon!", here's the
real trick that everybody loves. Whenever
you DM, if you have NPCs that your characters
are gonna meet, don't even think of a name
for them until they've walked up and talked
to the NPC. You'll produce some top quality
shit, my friend.
Wayne: Do you have examples? I can't remember.
Gir: Me neither. [crosstalk] That's the drawback.
Log: Whenever I was in charge— so, like,
the drawback is that they don't remember and
neither do I. So there's some characters I'm
pretty sure I changed the name of every time
they talked to them.
Trog: [crosstalk] I remember a couple.
Log: There's a couple.
Wayne: Nermal.
Log: Yeah, there's Nerm— well, Nermal's
just Nermal from Garfield, so that doesn't
count.
Wayne: You planned that one. You downloaded
a picture of Nermal and put it in roll20.
Log: Yeah.
Trog: Yeah, that one was right there.
Log: But there was a time where these boys,
and all of these boys were playin' in my campaign,
they walked up to a guy and that guy was just
a guy that I immediately thought up of, and
I got into my character voice and I said,
"Yeah man, what's up? Name's Faucet."
Trog: Oh yeah, Faucet!
Gir: Oh yeah, Faucet.
Wayne: Faucet was good.
Trog: Faucet was good. I think the most—
Log: And then I'm pretty sure I named an ogre
Ice Cream, [crosstalk] that was an ogre who
selled Ice Cream.
Gir: Yes, you did.
Trog: Yeah. I'm pretty sure.
Wayne: Yes, yes, his name was Ice Cream.
Trog: I remember Grill Skillman.
Log: Oh yeah! Gilly Skill— No, it was Gilly
Skillman.
Trog: [crosstalk] Gilly Skillman,
Wayne: A good name from an ancient campaign,
Baaulp's campaign, the first one we ever played
together, was Slappo the Dwarf, a jail guard
who just slapped your hands if you stuck them
out of the cell.
Trog: Yeah. That's a good character, but they're
looking for tips. Do we have any more tips
for DMing or playing D&D?
Baaulp: On character creation, I think—
for the longest time I thought "Eh, whatever",
but everyone seems to like the dumb characters.
I don't know how much of it is me playing
them, and how much it is because the characters
are good, but I basically just have two roles
whenever I make player characters or important
characters. A: They have to follow, like,
a simple set of rules, and when you're playing
the character, you have to abide by them.
They— I try to make them goofy, like Midet
is a bounty hunter, so he has to just cut
off peoples heads and like, that's it. Every
time you kill someone important like, "Hey,
how do we prove we actually got this guy?
I know, I'll chop their head off." Very good
being like— I guess he ended up not being
a pacifist, but he was very timid.
Trog: Yeah, no.
Baaulp: You just have to pick something [crosstalk]
and stick with it, if you can.
Log: Keep in mind, you just listed two characters
that nobody has heard of.
Trog: Keep in mind people listening have no
idea who these people are. But I understand
the advice.
Log: But like, to explain— well, this isn't
really a DMing part, but what Baaulp creates
consistently some of the best characters ever,
and it's because he just draws from himself
for a lot. He doesn't, like— he's playing
a character, but he's still not making himself
into something he's not. So it's very authentic
and good feeling.
Baaulp: Yeah, if you can take a little piece
of yourself, not like— don't make your character
YOU, but pick a quality that you already are,
I guess, and try to spin that into something.
[1:10:00]
Baaulp: It'll be good for beginners, too,
if you're not accustomed to putting yourself
in a really crazy roll where you're pretending
to be someone that you entirely aren't.
Wayne: Yeah, I won't name names, but there
are certain Dungeons and Dragons characters
that are something you entirely aren't, and
they did not turn out very good. Definitely
draw from yourself a little bit. Are you a
loud person? Play a loud character. Are you
a psychic that wants to battle for mind wits?
You play that.
Gir: Are you actually a psychic?
Wayne: My DM tip: make sure that you don't
make your characters do something just for
the sake of doing it that wouldn't already
be part of their personal motivations. Like,
if they're questing— if they're doing a
quest, and really their only characters personal
motivation is "We're doing this, we're gonna
get money at the end", but that's not the
characters goal, it makes for a very boring
time. That's something that I learned from
doing my campaign, where I sent the players
off following an old man, doing a mission—
a secretive mission that he couldn't tell
them anything about, because that was part
of the plot. I found very quickly, none of
the characters really had any investment,
because they were just kind of doing it because
I told them to. Player agency is really important,
and that's something I came to learn by doing
that campaign.
Log: Yeah, that's a big thing. That's probably
like, a lot of things people get all confused
about in these modern times. Don't try to
be The Adventure Zone, don't try to be Critical
Role or whatever.
Trog: Yeah, don't, definitely.
Log: Don't try and make a fuckin' story, alright?
You have— basically, you just come up with
a couple ideas, and don't expect— you have
to just make up stuff. I talked about coming
up with a guy named Faucet as a joke, but
it's just like— you have to do stuff like
that, because if you have humans as your players,
they will not follow a path. And if they have
to follow a path, it's kinda lame, right?
Wayne: My original idea with that campaign
was like, "Yeah, there's a bigger story, and
that's how I'm gonna piece together in these
individual, like, set-pieces, where they can
play around freely and do whatever they want
in those set-pieces, accomplishing the one
greater goal". But, I feel like what you were
saying about, is like, yeah, come up with
these concepts. Come up with your grand overarching
concepts, but let them come to that when they
come to that on their own. If you've got this
really cool idea for a big story thing, you
don't wanna force them into it. Don't just
walk them to it, let them stumble upon it,
I guess.
Gir: Yeah, I think it's really important to
remember that you don't be Mr. No Fun, and
force people along the way you want them to
go. You gotta let them fuck around every now
and then.
Log: And that's still hard, but—
Wayne: And even that, that still happens.
My campaign, I don't think it was bad, I just
think like, in terms of character development
and worldbuilding, it was boring just because
there was no— they were basically following
a line in terms of "Yeah, you need to go this
way and do this thing", they couldn't go to
the places they wanted to go. Once they were
in a place, it was like, whatever. I wasn't
like, "Okay, go to this house, then this house,
then this house!", do whatever, I dunno. Let
the players run free, let them find the things
you've put for them. Don't ensure that they
get them.
Gir: You've made up a world, let them explore
it.
Trog: I think the best way I've heard of describing
to make sure that stuff like that doesn't
happen is, you have to think about if you're
the DM, you're creating a world, and the world
should happen— events in the world should
happen whether or not your players are there
to witness them. So if you have something
planned, it shouldn't be, like, "Oh, the players
will go here, and that will trigger this to
happen." It should be more like, "Something
will happen at this place, and if the players
are around to see it, then they get to experience
it. If they're not, then maybe the events
will go down in a different way, but the event
still happens." Y'know?
Wayne: Remember that your world— it's not
like a video game, it's not a video game.
I think that's actually in general, not just
for this single concept, a good tip. But remember
that it's not a video game, it doesn't have
to work like a video game. It's not like these
things that are happening in your world are
not gonna render if your players aren't next
to it.
Trog: Yeah. Well, see, it's funny that you
mention that, because my next piece of advice
was actually just going to be, "Go and play
Divinity 2. Go buy it on Steam." Go play Divinity
2, because it's really good, and I dunno.
Playing that game— if you don't know what
Divinity 2 is, it's a, uh—
Wayne: CRPG.
Trog: CRPG. Really good, you don't have to
play the first one to play the second one.
I never played the first one and i absolutely
loe the second one. But playing that game
just got me like... SUPER back into wanting
to DM again. And I dunno if it's just the
fact that it's an RPG or just the fact that
it's like, I dunno. Something about that game.
[crosstalk] Maybe, y'know—
Wayne: It's a really cool fantasy world.
[1:15:00]
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: It's a really cool story with really
cool grander concepts, and also I think one
thing I love about it is the individual aspect
of every sidequest.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Every little side quest is like—
some sidequests might just be like, "Hey,
there are these two cows. They're people.
They were turned into cows. Go get them a
potion. Pick which one you want to become
a human again." and then that's over.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: But then another sidequest is this
big, giant, crazy thing. That's another thing
in D&D. Make little, silly, weird things happen.
Or cool things happen.
Gir: Be creative.
Wayne: It's a fantasy world. You could run
into a talking frog that wants you to bring
it a huge loaf of bread. Some shit like that,
I dunno.
Gir: Or doesn't even have to be a fantasy
world. It could be a fuckin' sci-fi world.
Wayne: Well, yeah. Whatever—
Trog: Yeah, exactly.
Gir: [crosstalk] It could be cowboy world.
Wayne: It's still fantasy no matter what.
Like, you're playing D&D, you don't get away
from the fantasy.
Gir: My point is you don't have to do high
fantasy if you don't want to.
Trog: Nah.
Wayne: Don't play your game in the real world!
Don't do that!
Baaulp: Don't LARP. LARPing is bad.
Gir: [crosstalk] Hey, don't— give it a shot!
Wayne: That's not what I mean.
Gir: Maybe you have a good idea.
Trog: To generalize that advice, I guess what
I'm saying is don't be afraid to take inspiration
from other forms of media, as long as you
aren't like, [crosstalk] completely ripping
them off.
Gir: Straight copying it.
Wayne: Oh no, you can do that too.
Trog: Well...
Gir: What?
Wayne: One of my highest points from my campaign
is just making the final boss Geese Howard
[crosstalk] but changing his name to Swan
Howard.
Trog: Yeah, that's different. That's fine.
Gir: He means like, plot line and everything.
Trog: Yeah, and I mean maybe—
Wayne: Don't rip it off one-to-one.
Trog: I shouldn't say that, because I dunno,
maybe your players would enjoy just playing
the plot of something. But, I will say, definitely
don't be afraid to take inspiration from other
forms of media.
Wayne: And your Samurai Jack campaign, that
we’re playing right now.
Gir: This may shock you, but we took inspiration
from Dragon Ball a lot.
Trog: Which is really funny, because I actually
haven't watched the new Samurai Jack or anything,
I just had that show—
Baaulp: It was bad.
Trog: I haven't watched that show in forever,
I just had it on my mind, and I was like,
"I should make a D&D campaign where they're
in the future, and they have to go back to
the past." And so I did. And you can watch
it, every Tuesday, on wayneradiotv.twitch.com.
Log: Yeah! Yeah! [crosstalk] Yeah! Yeah!
Baaulp: .twitch.com.
Trog: That's not— that's— yeah. [crosstalk]
Go there.
Gir: That's not the URL.
Wayne: wayneradiotv.twitch.com.
Trog: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Log: Yeah.
Wayne: Buy it. Go there. Buy the domain for
us.
Log: Also, my last thing that I'm gonna say
for this. If your players don't know about
UA classes, if you wanna make things easy
for yourself, just don't tell them.
Trog: Yeah, don't tell them.
Log: Don't let them know about Artificer or
Mystic.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: [crosstalk] Like I said before, you gotta
let your—
Wayne: No, it's good!
Log: You gotta expect your players to just
do whatever. So, like, you gotta expect a
wrench to be thrown into any grand plans you
have. But if you let somebody play as Mystic
or Artificer Gunsmith, they will drive a truck
into your well-tuned machine, and you will
have to pick up the pieces.
Trog: Basically, the best thing you can do,
is read what your players can actually do
before you start planning things out.
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: Because you could plan something out,
and have it completely fold because you didn't
realize that one of your magic users in their
party has like, some random spell that completely
ruins whatever puzzle or anything you have
planned.
Wayne: My favorite example of that was in
the Pathfinder campaign we played, Baaulp's
campaign, the very first one we played. Where
Baaulp had a maze, that was— wait, no no
no, [crosstalk] this was Trog's campaign.
Gir: This was our current one.
Wayne: No no no, no, this was Trog's Pathfinder
campaign.
Gir: Oh.
Trog: Mhmm.
Wayne: Where I played as a teleporting gnome—
Gir: Oh, yeah.
Wayne: The funny thing was, this was a little
bit into the campaign, this wasn't the very
first thing we did. So the DM knew that I
was a teleporting gnome, and still put a maze
full of mines, that I just teleported past
the entire thing. [crosstalk] It's that kind
of thing.
Trog: I remember that.
Log: Yeah, I tried to have a fight with a
superpowered satyr on a rooftop, but Wayne
picked Mystic, so he just, "Oh yeah, I jump
50 feet to the next rooftop and leave!".
Trog: Yeah.
Gir: Here's the thing, like—
Wayne: Hey, I thought that was a cool solution
to that fight.
Log: [crosstalk] I mean— ??? We made it
work.
Gir: If your major obstacle is a hole, don't—
make sure your people can't all just fly over
the hole.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: I mean, you can still have that stuff
too, [crosstalk] but make sure there's more
to it than that.
Gir: My point is—
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: Double check that your obstacle and their
spells aren't, like, [crosstalk] obvious.
Trog: Lemme let you guys in on a little secret,
too. Anti-magic zones, counter-spell, [crosstalk]
and de-spell. Use those a lot.
Gir: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. All that,
too.
Wayne: But at the same time, don't go crazy
with it, [crosstalk] because it's just kinda
bullshit if it's just like, "Nope, nope. No
magic here."
Trog: No, yeah. Yeah.
Wayne: Or at least give them a way to fix
it, [crosstalk] like, turn it off.
Trog: Use it in places that is appropriate,
I'd say.
Wayne: Alright, let's move on, next question.
Trog: Alright. Next question is... okay, well...
I see now, looking at this document further
down, that Baaulp did not actually put the
REAL names of the people, and instead but
the names that they are in Discord, which
everybody changes those constantly, [crosstalk]
so I don't know who this actually is
Baaulp: Aw crap. Sorry.
Trog: BEEF—
[1:20:00]
Baaulp: I just copy and pasted.
Trog: Yeah, I noticed.
Wayne: Beef?
Trog: Beef asked, "Favorite sword?"
Log: Gotta be rapier or cutlass. Easy.
Trog: Oh, so you're goin' like, g— [crosstalk]
I thought he was asking, like, specifically,
what is your—
Wayne: Sword style?
Trog: Like, if you— like... A sword.
Log: Well, like... how many different named
swords are there?
Wayne: Coolest sword: Cera Symmetry from Monster
Hunter.
Trog: That's a pretty good— that's a damn
good choice.
Gir: Fierce Deity Link's sword.
Trog: That's a cool one.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Uh, do other—
Wayne: Fierce Deedee.
Gir: Deedee.
Baaulp: Do other types of things count? 'Cause
I'm gonna pick— I'm gonna be that guy, I'm
gonna pick swordbreaker. 'Cause I like the
idea of someone whipping out a dagger, and—
Imagine you don't know what it is.
Wayne: It's not a sword, sword's in the name,
[crosstalk] it doesn't make it a sword.
Baaulp: Swordbreaker.
Trog: I don't know what a swordbreaker is.
Baaulp: A knife is a small sword.
Wayne: I guess so.
Trog: I guess so.
Baaulp: So there you go. I'm that guy, I'll
break your sword, [crosstalk] and then I'll
stab you with a regular sword.
Gir: Good question. Next question.
Trog: No wait, I didn't do mine. Wait, did
everybody do theirs? I think— y'know, I
was thinking about it, and I had one in mind
until Wayne brought up Monster Hunter, and
then I was like, I think it's probably gotta
be just like— I dunno, it's been so long
since I've played a Monster Hunter game at
this point.
Gir: ???.
Trog: I say that, but it's literally been
like, 3 months. That's too long for me.
Wayne: Oh, you know what's also great? The
Nargacuga longswords. Those are awesome.
Trog: But, I think the concept of both the
Switch Axe and the Charge Blade are both really
cool. I'm really into weapons that can turn
into different weapons, so I think— I don't
know if those really count as a sword. I guess
at least the Switch Axe does, part of the
time, but it's probably gotta be that.
Log: If I have to give a named weapon, um—
You guys know Ike, he's in Smash Brothers.
Wayne: Mhmm.
Log: In the Fire Emblem games and stuff, and
the sword he has in Smash Brothers, his sword
is named Ragnell, and it lets him counter-attack
people from any distance. At least, I'm pretty
sure— well, at least he can counter attack
people from 2 spaces away. And that's great,
because all the wizards come at you with their
AI and they start fighting Ike, and then he
just slams them from 20 miles away. It's good.
[crosstalk] Aether's in that game, and it
makes him heal for as much damage as he does.
Wayne: Good sword.
Trog: Good sword.
Wayne: Did everybody give their answer? We
need more short ones.
Trog: Yeah, I think.
Gir: More short ones.
Wayne: I think everyone did it. Alright. [crosstalk]
Next question.
Trog: Alright, this is a short one—
Wayne: I have one I'd like to read too. I'll
do it at the end.
Trog: Next question is from Kappa Mikey who
asks, "What's your favorite Minecraft block?".
[crosstalk] What is it, guys?
Log: Diamond.
Gir: ???.
Baaulp: Yeah, if you say anything but diamond,
[crosstalk] you're wrong.
Trog: I think it's unanimously diamond.
Wayne: No, [crosstalk] my favorite—
Log: Yeah. I don't fuckin' play Minecraft,
it's diamond.
Wayne: My favorite Minecraft block is... bedrock.
'Cause you can't break it.
Trog: Oh... alright. Here is a question from
Unmistakably Crash Bandicoot, who asks, "What
video game do you think would make a good
movie, or at least a movie you'd want to see?".
Wayne: Dude, I want live action Kingdom Hearts
II. [crosstalk] That'd be the craziest shit.
Trog: Oh my god.
Wayne: Question answered. [crosstalk] Next.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: No video— What video game works as
a movie? What video game movies have been
good? [crosstalk] Have there been?
Trog: None.
Gir: Heavy Rain.
Baaulp: Because they always pick action games,
but those are structured in a way that you
can't really wrap them or fit them in a specific
2 hour narrative without completely butchering
them and having to do all sorts of weird things.
And video game movies have such a tinge to
them, like, if anyone says, "Oh, this is inspired
by a video game", that's pretty much a code
word for "guaranteed to be bad".
Wayne: Well, the thing is, you just have to
lay into that aspect of it. Like, the fucking
Resident Evil movie with that Wesker fight
at the end? [crosstalk]
Trog: Oh my god.
Wayne: That's the most amazing fucking thing
ever.
Trog: Something that just doesn't ever happen
at all in the games.
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: I have one in mind where I know it would
be bad, but I'd still like to see them hurt
themselves try to make it. I'd like to see
somebody fumble over making a Fallout movie.
Wayne: Oh, it would suck.
Baaulp: Yeah, [crosstalk] that'd be so bad.
Gir: That would be like, the funniest disaster.
Wayne: It would be so bad.
Trog: Honestly, I thought you were gonna say
Half-Life.
Gir: No.
Wayne: Half-Life could make a good movie.
Baaulp: 'Cause, Fallout is a—
Gir: You give J.J. a few more years.
Baaulp: Even the first person shooter ones,
Fallout is like an RPG. Can you imagine seeing
a Fallout movie where some action dude, like
Baptista, is doing flips and shooting a laser
pistol?
Wayne: I think a Half-Life movie adaption,
I think that might be inevitable. I think
that'll happen.
Trog: [crosstalk] Maybe.
Gir: J.J. Abrams. already said he plans to
do it.
Trog: That's crazy.
Gir: That and a Portal movie.
Wayne: That could be really— [crosstalk]
I think both of those could make really good
movies.
Trog: Alright, a Portal movie sounds fucking
stupid. There's literally one character—
there's two characters in all of Portal.
Wayne: Wait, yeah. I just realized what Portal
is.
Baaulp: Portal is puzzles. It's puzzles.
Trog: Yeah, you cannot turn— [crosstalk]
let's make a movie out of fuckin' Poyo Poyo.
Wayne: It would be a completely different
thing, and I take back the fact that I accidentally
said that it would be good. A Half-Life movie
could be fucking awesome, I think a Portal
movie would be nothing like the game.
Gir: What about a Left 4 Dead movie?
Wayne: That would be generic.
Trog: Eh, I don't like zombies.
[1:25:00]
Wayne: I think one of the reasons Left 4 Dead
works is because it is kind of generic. It
kinda plays off just like a basic horror movie.
Gir: That's true.
Wayne: That's even how the levels start and
end, it's a movie poster.
Baaulp: I know there was a Ratchet and Clank
movie, but there was also supposed to— I
don't know if it ever got released, there
was supposed to be a Sly Cooper movie.
Trog: Really?
Wayne: [crosstalk] I don't think that's happened
yet.
Gir: Yeah, there was.
Baaulp: Yeah, there was a trailer for it as
some point.
Wayne: I think that's still in the works.
Gir: Yeah, I think that's still in the works.
Wayne: Or maybe the Ratchet and Clank movie
bombed and they cancelled it.
Baaulp: Well, the Ratchet and Clank movie
got like—
Gir: It did decently.
Baaulp: Yeah, I don't know how well that did.
Trog: Did that have theatrical release?
Gir: [crosstalk] Yes.
Wayne: Yeah. It was big.
Trog: Wow, I had no idea.
Wayne: It came out with the game that was
really, really good.
Trog: Yeah, the remake or whatever.
Log: Now that I think about it, I feel like
you can't really make a good movie with a
popular game, really. Half-Life might get
close, but name any popular game, it'll probably
be a bad movie, ultimately. Nobody's got a
track record with popular games being made
into good movies.
Wayne: The newest God of War could probably
make a cool movie, [crosstalk] considering
they tried to make it like a movie in some
facets.
Log: Maybe, but like, what's the point?
Gir: Uncharted. Uncharted would make a decent
movie.
Wayne: I would hate it.
Log: Hey, I'm not done! I'm not done. I got
my idea for a movie I'd wanna see. So, a movie
about any of the games from Failbetter. Failbetter
makes like, Fallen London, and Sunless Sea,
and Sunless Skies and stuff. And those are
just top-down games where you sail a ship
or fly a spaceship and stuff, and a lot of
the stuff transpires in text, and it's just
supposed to be a creepy game where you read
about weird creatures and strange places and
stuff. I think that anybody who takes the
time to make a movie off of that will be good,
because they don't have any stupid scenes
that they can just copy one-to-one. They have
to read to do it. So they'll have to make
something that's true to form, and would be—
it'd be cool to see the visuals of it, I think.
There's shit where like, "Oh, this is just
a weird log in space that people live on that
just grows fungus everywhere, and everybody's
covered in fungus. All the old people come
here to get covered in fungus."
Wayne: They love it. Alright.
Baaulp: Now, I just have one last note. I
like Log's idea, I think you just gotta get
weird. I wanna see— now that I think about
it, I have an idea—
Wayne: RUNESCAPE THE MOVIE.
Baaulp: A Katamari Damacy movie made like
the Godzilla movie. ???.
Wayne: That could be awesome.
Gir: Wayne just made me think, could you imagine
a RuneScape movie where you just see somebody
in the background shouting, "I WILL PAY FOR
A GIRLFRIEND."
Wayne: Yeah, you got a movie where the events
of the movie are a regular video game movie
script, it's just lofty and bad, but in the
background there's just a dude hitting a tree
the exact same way over and over and over,
[crosstalk] and he never moves away.
Gir: "2K for GF."
Wayne: And then occasionally the tree just
disappears, and he moves to a different one.
Log: Hey, I just gotta say, fuck Sword Art
Online. I've never seen a single episode of
it, but I fuckin' hate it. That shit's dumb,
right? They don't even have something on that
level, like buying gf or whatever, right?
They aren't with it, right? Has anybody seen
an episode of that?
Trog: I don't—
Wayne: No.
Baaulp: No.
Gir: No.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Why would any of us—
Trog: None of us have seen a single episode
of that anime.
Gir: We don't watch garbage!
Log: It's bullshit. I remember— I've only
ever seen one or two episodes of .hack//Sign,
but there was a scene from the show where
there were just players pinned to a dartboard,
and they're throwing darts at them, and they're
like, "Hey, why are they pinned to a dartboard?"
"Oh, they did some packet editing to change
the color of their clothes." "Oh.", and I
just thought, "Alright, that's good, I like
that. [crosstalk] I'd much rather have them
buying gf, but still, that's something."
Wayne: That is pretty good.
Log: Fuck Sword Art Online.
Trog: Uh, okay. My answer is, I agree with
Wayne saying Kingdom Hearts the Movie. Live
action movie. I would see it day one, I'd
stand outside for a week. Beyond that, though,
I think Mario Bros., a sequel with all of
the same actors.
Gir: Like the dead ones, even.
Log: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Necromancy.
Trog: CGI. [crosstalk] Carrie Fisher's gonna
be in the new Star Wars.
Baaulp: Hologram.
Wayne: No, necromancy. I think the CGI approach
is lazy, I think we actually have to bring
them back.
Baaulp: Did you hear that Carrie Fisher is
gonna be in the next Star Wars movie?
Wayne: Yeah.
Gir: 'Cause they had some of the filming done
already.
Baaulp: That's so... agh.
Gir: They're like, "Welp, we might as well
use it."
Log: Man oh man, I can't wait to see a CGI
Lou Albano.
Trog: Yeah. Man.
Log: He'll look so good.
Gir: Next question?
Trog: Alright, this one— I'm gonna make
a rule on this one, and that's; you only get
one chance to answer this question, and that's
it, okay? Are we all in—
Gir: Alright.
Trog: Alright, you get one chance to answer
this question. Cosmic Cow asks, "Favorite
clown name?"
[1:30:00]
Trog: You get one. You can't take it back
once you say it.
Wayne: You have to edit in dramatic music
for the silence here.
Trog: Yeah, put in the "Who Wants to Be a
Millionaire?" music.
["Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?" music starts]
Log: Does it have to be a real—
Wayne: That's what I'm hearing in my head
right now.
Trog: Yeah.
Log: Does it have to be a real clown name
that we've seen?
Trog: No.
Gir: Got it. Dancing Jacob.
Trog: Final answer?
Gir: Final answer.
Trog: Alright. We'll see who wins at the end.
Wayne: Oh no.
Trog: This is really hard.
Wayne: What I wanna say might be funny, it
might not.
Trog: [crosstalk] That's the trick, man.
Gir: We'll cut it out if its not.
Wayne: I mean, do you wanna hear— I was
just like, thinking of nothing. Do you wanna
hear the first name that popped into my head?
Trog: I dunno, is that your final answer?
You get one choice.
Wayne: I guess so. It's gonna take too long.
I'll just say it, 'cause I don't even care.
The first thing that popped in my head was
Toffee King, Spitter of Acid.
Log: Not bad, not bad.
Trog: That's a pretty— that doesn't sound
very jovial, but...
Wayne: Exactly, and that's why I don't think
I like it.
Log: I dunno, I come up with infinite names,
[crosstalk] I just gotta go with one.
Baaulp: Zap.
Log: Did you just say Zack?
Log: Okay.
Trog: Alright.
Gir: Spell that for us?
Baaulp: Z-A-P.
Gir: Zap.
Log: Oh, Zap. Why did it sound like you were
saying Zack?
Baaulp: I dunno. 'Cause I have a nasally voice?
I dunno.
Log: Anyways, mine is DJ Caterpillar, [crosstalk]
and that's what I'm goin' with.
Trog: Pretty good.
Gir: Is he a DJ or clown? It's confusing.
Trog: Oh man. Puttin' the pressure on me.
I'm gonna go with... I'm gonna go with Dimmy
Pickles.
Wayne: Okay. Okay.
Log: Dimmy Pickles.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] That sounds real familiar!
Trog: Dimmy Pickles.
Wayne: I need a retake. [crosstalk] I know
you said only one, I have to break the rules.
Gir: No.
Trog: No! You don't get a retake! There's
no retake.
Baaulp: No! No!
Wayne: It wasn't a clown name, I just said
some bullshit! [crosstalk] What clown's gonna
spit acid? You wanna burn those children?
You wanna ruin their lives?
Baaulp: That was your one chance!
Gir: Too bad! Sorry!
Trog: You can do another one, but we're not
gonna cut it out. Everybody shame Wayne. If
you're listening to this, write in the comments,
[crosstalk] "I shame you, Wayne."
Baaulp: Throw an egg at his house!
Trog: [crosstalk] And now you get your second.
Log: Boooo! Booooo!
Trog: You get your second one.
Log: You should've picked the right one the
first time!
Baaulp: If you're listening on the phone,
tap your phone aggressively. Shake him up,
he's in there.
Trog: Throw your phone on the concrete and
yell.
Gir: Shout "Crappy Clowner!"
Log: "You suck!"
Gir: Fuckin' spit it out!
Baaulp: Say the clown name, motherfucker!
Log: Why'd you ask for a second try if you
didn't have a name!?
Trog: This is the future of podcasting, you're
fucking this up for all of us!
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Say the clown name! Say
the fucking clown name! Don't say—
Wayne: I can't think of a name! I'm thinking
of a specific thing!
Gir: [crosstalk] Clown me!
Baaulp: If the next word that comes out of
your mouth is not a clown name, I'm gonna
be so fucking pissed.
Wayne: Michael, the Fastest Clown.
Trog: Alright.
Wayne: The Speedior.
Trog Hey kids, let's go see Michael!
Gir: Nah, [crosstalk] I'd rather go see Dancing
Jacob.
Trog: You fucked it up.
Wayne: You can't cut out his title!
Log: Jotex the Speedior is my favorite clown.
Wayne: That's what it was! I couldn't think
of his name being Jotex, that was what I wanted
to say.
Trog: Alright.
Gir: [crosstalk] Dancing Jacob wins, I swear.
Wayne: Alright.
Wayne: One more real question.
Trog: This was a failure.
["Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?" music stops]
Trog: Alright. Wait, you said one more? [crosstalk]
How many are we doing?
Wayne: One more real question. Last one.
Trog: One more real question? Alright.
Wayne: And then I got one.
Trog: Piglover asks, "Everyone always asks
what you would eat for your last meal, but
what is the worst food you could give to your
mortal enemy for their last meal?"
Wayne: Immortality apple.
Gir: [crosstalk] Feces.
Trog: No.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Wait, but that would negate
it!
Trog: No, no, no. I'm gonna put down— I'mma
lay down some ground rules here, and I'm gonna
say it has to be food.
Baaulp: Aw, I was gonna say dirt.
Gir: Alright, we're not crawling into fucking
MBMBaM territory and questioning what is and
isn't food.
Log: Rye and pumpernickel swirl bread.
Wayne: Yay, I'm Log's worst enemy, and I get
a great sandwich!
Log: Alright, but I'm gonna stick a wasp underneath
your seat as you're about to sit down.
Wayne: God, fuckin' just— worst enemy's
worst last meal. Alright, fuckin' bowl of
nails! [crosstalk] Eat up!
Trog: No, I said it has to be food! It has
to be something that someone in the world
has eaten before.
Wayne: Poop.
Trog: Fuck— no.
Gir: That's what I said!
Log: [crosstalk] A lightbulb.
Trog: You are not— this is not the spirit
of the question, I feel like.
Log: A television set.
Wayne: Who's eaten a TV set?
Log: [crosstalk] Someone has done it.
Baaulp: Someone ate a plane once.
Gir: Do you remember when you were in high
school, and someone would say, "Hey, dump
all your food into my plate, and I'll eat
it!"
Trog: What? [crosstalk] No.
Baaulp: No? Who did that?
Gir: It was like, somebody's soda, and macaroni,
[crosstalk] and a pizza, and fuckin' chips.
There was some kid that would eat that!
Trog: Oh, gross.
Wayne: What school of a zoo did you go to?
Gir: There was some kid that would just mix
a bunch of random shit, and they're like,
"If you give me $5, I'll eat this." That's
what I'd feed them.
Baaulp: Are you sure you weren't hallucinating
on a pig farm?
Gir: No! Okay, I guess you guys didn't go
to school with idiots like I did.
Wayne: One time I took an overripe banana,
and a little bit of milk, and some turkey
and cheese, and wrapped it up— and mushed
it all together, wrapped it up in a paper
towel, and I tried to give it to this kid
I hate and told him it was a cheeseburger.
Log: Oh shit, give them Bardonic ramen!
Trog: [crosstalk] Oh, alright. No way. That's
it. That is it.
Gir: Yeah! Bardonic— yep! Yep! Bardonic
ramen.
[1:35:00]
Log: Hey, for viewers—
Gir: We're not explaining it.
Trog: [crosstalk] We have some homework for
you guys.
Wayne: It'll be in the description, you have
to explain it.
Log: Bardonic ramen is blue like Sonic the
Hedgehog, bitches!
Wayne: What did he cook it in? Powerade? What
was it?
Log: Yeah, yeah, [crosstalk] it's Powerade.
Trog: I'm pretty sure it was Powerade.
Wayne: It's ramen boiled in Powerade, and
then I think he adds— what was the yellow
aspect of it, if it's Bardonic?
Log: Like a banana or something.
Gir: [crosstalk] The flavoring.
Trog: No, I think it was the ramen.
Wayne: Was it a banana?
Trog: I think the ramen was it.
Wayne: Oh no, it was the chicken flavoring!
Trog: Oh yeah, that's right!
Wayne: It is blue Powerade ramen, and he still
adds the chicken flavoring.
Trog: I'm pretty sure he puts sprinkles or
something on it, too.
Wayne: Yeah, something like that.
Log: Yeah.
Gir: He puts those ??? in it.
Trog: Anyway, go check the description for
that video and watch it so you can get this
joke.
Baaulp: Yeah.
Log: [crosstalk] Want me to tell them the
name of the YouTuber?
Trog: No. Pause the podcast, go watch that
video, and come back.
Log: Yeah, just look for Bardonic ramen. It's
available in all stores.
Baaulp: I was gonna say— I was gonna reference
this one time when I was a kid, when Sun Chips
first came out, I really liked them, so I
bought a huge bag of Sun Chips, I ate the
whole bag, it was like a party size bag. I
felt really gross and I vomited, I was gonna
make them eat that, but nah. It's Bardonic
ramen.
Trog: You can't make somebody eat throw up
as their last meal.
Baaulp: No, not my throw up! I mean, eat Sun
Chips until they threw up.
Trog: Eat Sun Chips! "What's the worst thing
you could give to your mortal enemy?" "Uh,
here's a bag of Garden Salsa Sun Chips."
Wayne: [crosstalk] But a lot of them.
Gir: It's cheating to say you'd give them
so much they puke, 'cause then you could just
say, [crosstalk] "Oh, I give them ice cream
until they die."
Baaulp: Yeah, your meal's the whole bag!
Trog: All you can eat slime. You have to eat
until they die.
Gir: Slime.
Wayne: Oh yeah, my last meal is Gak!
Gir: Play-Doh! [crosstalk] Play-Doh!
Trog: I'm pretty sure it's mostly corn syurp,
so...
Baaulp: Yeah, it probably wouldn't be that
bad.
Gir: [crosstalk] Make them eat Play-Doh.
Wayne: You probably couldn't swallow it! It
was probably too sticky.
Gir: Glue?
Baaulp: [crosstalk] We're going down a dangerous
road here.
Wayne: You probably couldn't swallow a wad
of corn starch, I think it's too dry, I dunno.
Log: Eat some lead pita chips.
Baaulp: Was that the last question or do we
have another question?
Wayne: [crosstalk] I have the last question.
Gir: Wayne's got the final question.
Trog: Alright.
Wayne: Alright, are you guys ready?
Baaulp: [crosstalk] Yeah.
Gir: Yeah.
Trog: Yeah.
Wayne: Alright, so, somebody joined our Discord
server last night, after the Pixel Ripped
stream. Their name is Little Green Man, and
the only thing they've done in the server
so far is go in the podcast channel and ask
this question, in all caps, "HAVE YOU EVER
BEEN CAUGHT ON FIRE?"
Gir: Yeah, somebody caught me being aflame
once.
Baaulp: Hey, I got you covered. The answer
is all of us, we're all dead.
Trog: Oh, [crosstalk] you weren't supposed
to say that 'till the season finale.
Gir: Okay, no, I can wrap this around to the
very start, [crosstalk] where I was not on
fire, but my friends bushes were.
Baaulp: Oh, do that.
Log: Well, who gives a fuck about that?
Wayne: Yeah?
Gir: His family, when they went outside and
saw their bushes on fire.
Wayne: That's like someone asks, "Hey, you
ever broken a bone?" "No, my friend did, though."
Log: There was somebody I knew that did a
fuckin' little stunt, where they would spray
perfume on themselves and then light it on
fire, [crosstalk] and then put it out.
Trog: What the fuck?
Log: Apparently it didn't burn them, [crosstalk]
so I guess that's okay.
Gir: It's 'cause it was burning the perfume,
not them.
Log: Yeah, yeah.
Gir: You do the same thing with alcohol.
Log: But yeah, that's what they would do.
Gir: I don't think anyone here has ever been
lit aflame.
Trog: No. I have not.
Log: Nuh uh.
Baaulp: No.
Gir: Kind of a weak final question there.
Log: Maybe we shouldn't have answered it.
Wayne: That was the point.
Log: Well, you should have told us.
Trog: You should have said, "Here's a question,
don't answer this one, though."
Wayne: Alright, then I have another one we
won't answer— [crosstalk] or we could, it's
up to you. Ready?
Trog: Alright. I'll try, I'll always try.
Wayne: This one is from... do you want me
to read the Discord name, because that was
what Baaulp was doing? Which is muscle emoji,
lip emoji, again lip emoji, thumbs up.
Trog: I think that's, uh—
Wayne: Its GrauBun, I know who it is.
Trog: Oh, yeah yeah yeah.
Wayne: This question is from GrauBun. "Credit
card number and social security number?"
Gir: Yes, you can tell me.
Trog: Ooh.
Wayne: Yes, please give them to us. Put those
in the Discord.
Trog: Yeah, if you wanna participate at home,
write your credit card and social security
number in the comment box.
Wayne: Down below in the comments.
Trog: [crosstalk] And leave it for me.
Log: Yeah.
Gir: Don't forget the security code!
Wayne: Also, I'll need your first name, [crosstalk]
and your last name.
Log: First name.
Trog: Just that.
Gir: [crosstalk] Your home address.
Log: First name, Tamers.
Trog: Your first name, your nickname, [crosstalk]
and your favorite flavor of ice cream.
Wayne: Your fun name.
Gir: If you're unfortunate and don't have
one of those funny plastic shopping cards,
go ahead and just— you can pay us and we'll
send you one.
Trog: Who needs those anymore? I can just
walk into pet stores and steal things.
Gir: I'll just squeak everything I steal.
Wayne: I think the concept of middle names
should be changed, and they should just be
called fun names. [crosstalk] Because nobody
uses them, they're just for fun.
Gir: Central names.
Trog: Can I change my fun name?
Gir: [crosstalk] No.
Wayne: Yeah, it's for fun.
Trog: [crosstalk] Can I change it to Dimmy
Pickles?
Gir: You can only do it for fun. You gotta
pick one.
Wayne: Yeah.
Trog: Sick.
Wayne: Alright everybody, well, thank you
for listening to The Podcast #1: The Future
of Podcasting, now The Past of Podcasting.
Tune in next time for The Podcast #2.
Log: I dare you to find it if you can.
Baaulp: Charge your phone, because our podcast
was so powerful, you probably have 1% battery
left. Go.
Wayne: It absolutely is, [crosstalk] check
your fuckin' batteries.
Gir: That was Baaulp hiding inside your phone.
Baaulp: I burst your battery open with my
sharp front teeth, and I suck out the power.
Trog: Should we plug the Discord or anything?
Or should we plug the stream?
[1:40:00]
Wayne: Absolutely. Look down below at the
Discord. It's in the description, you can
click the link, it's an invite link. You can
either join the Discord in your web browser
or in your programs. Also, check out twitch.tv/wayneradiotv,
the Twitch stream that this podcast is affiliated
with, where we play all kinds of fun video
games. I play them.
Gir: We're there too.
Baaulp: [crosstalk] I watch you play them.
Wayne: They're there, that's kind of just
the draw.
Trog: Yeah. That's it.
Wayne: [crosstalk] Sometimes we play them
together.
Gir: We'll be there.
Trog: If you enjoyed this, you'll probably
enjoy that. It's like this but somehow even
less coordinated.
Log: Also, check out One Piece. It's pretty
good.
Wayne: Check out logmore.tumblr.com for the
quickest art. I mean coolest art.
Gir: And because we're here at the very end,
I'd like to say, if you listened to the entire
thing, thank you. If you just skipped here,
go fuck yourself.
Wayne: No one— who skips to the last 10
seconds of a podcast?
Trog: I do.
Gir: [crosstalk] Demons.
Baaulp: That's the juicy bit.
Wayne: Buh, I wonder— I open up an episode
of my favorite podcast, "Mmm, I wonder how
the ended this one!"
Gir: They're like, "Oh, that conversation
was boring, let me see if they get onto something
different."
Trog: No, no, no, Wayne, you have it wrong.
You open up an episode of your least favorite
podcast and skip to the end.
Gir: "Yeah, fuck these guys! I'm just gonna
listen to the end!"
Baaulp: Hey, everyone, shoutout to, uh, hot
dog.
Trog: Great. Great.
Wayne: Shoutout. [crosstalk] Followers.
Trog: Great. Great. Great. Where do I begin?
[crosstalk] Fuck you.
Wayne: Goodnight everybody.
Trog: Fuck you.
Gir: Fuck you.
[outro song "I Love Classic Cars" by Yin Xia
plays (1:41:17 - 1:41:32)]